<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="save_changes">Save Changes</string>
    <string name="terms_text_manage">By clicking on Save. I &lt;br&gt;agree to the &lt;a&gt;&lt;font color="#0267b1"&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</string> 
    <string name="messages_sent_to">Text messages are sent to:</string>
    <string name="notification_change">Change</string>
    <string name="mobile_device_not_verified">Your mobile device isn\'t verified yet.\nPlease text "Yes" to 347268 to complete text enrollement.</string>
    <string name="enable_texts">Enable Texts</string>
    <string name="enable_push_alerts">Enable Push Alerts</string>
    <string name="text">Text</string>
    <string name="push_alerts">Push\n Alerts</string>
    <string name="notification_on">ON</string>
    <string name="notification_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="manage_your_account_title">Manage Your Accounts</string>
    <string name="monitor_your_spending_title">Monitor Your Spending</string>
    <string name="maximize_your_rewards_title">Maximize Your Rewards</string>
    <string name="show_notification_list">+</string>
    <string name="hide_notification_list">-</string>
    <string name="push_progress_registration_loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="push_progress_get_title">Discover</string>
    <string name="previous_account_title">A previous account has set up Push Alerts on this phone.  What would you like to do?</string>
    <string name="keep_current_settings">Keep current account settings</string>
    <string name="remove_current_settings">Remove previous account settings</string>
    <string name="enroll_in_reminders">Enroll in Mobile Reminders</string>
    <string name="enroll_in_reminders_text">Monitor your spending and account activity with Mobile Reminders sent right to your mobile phone.</string>
    <string name="fees_may_apply">Text and data fees may apply</string>
    <string name="push_enroll">Enroll</string>
    <string name="push_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="push_alerts_are_available">Push Alerts Are Now Available</string>
    <string name="push_alerts_are_available_text">You can now sign up to have important account updates and reminders sent directly to your phone. Tap on Manage Alerts below to select what alerts you would like to recieve.</string>
    <string name="manage_alerts">Manage Alerts</string>
    <string name="account_home">Account Home</string>
   	<string name="another_user_registered">A previous account has set up Push Alerts on this phone. What would you like to do?</string>
   	<string name="keep_current_settings">Keep current account settings</string>
   	<string name="remove_current_settings">Remove previous account settings</string>
   	<string name="push_manage_save_success">Text and Push Alerts settings have been updated.</string>
    
    <string name="notifcation_terms_and_condtions_header">Mobile Reminders, Fraud Alerts and Push Alerts Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="notification_terms_agreement">By signing up to receive Mobile Reminders and/or Fraud Alerts (“Text Messages”) or Push Alerts (“Push Alerts”), you agree to the following Terms of Use. By accessing or using Text Messages or Push Alerts, you agree to be bound by these Terms and all terms incorporated by reference.  If you do not agree to these Terms, do not sign up for or use Text Messages or Push Alerts.  DFS means Discover Products Inc. and its affiliates."</string>
    <string name="use_of_texts_header">Use of Text Messages</string>
    <string name="use_of_texts_text_1">Our Text Messages allow you to request and receive text messages about your Account with us. It is your responsibility to determine if your mobile service provider supports text messaging and your mobile device is capable of receiving text messages. Our Text Messages are subject to the terms and conditions of your agreement(s) with your mobile device carrier. You acknowledge that our Text Messages are sent to you without being encrypted and will include information pertaining to your Account, although we will not include your complete account number or social security number in any unencrypted text. You are responsible for any fees imposed by your mobile device carrier of any kind whatsoever.</string>
    <string name="use_of_push_header">Use of Push Alerts</string>
    <string name="use_of_push_text_1">Our Push Alerts enable you to receive push notifications through your device’s push notification system.  These Push Alerts allow you to receive new alerts even if you are logged out of the Discover app. These Push Alerts can also have action links that will open the Discover App so that you can take immediate action.  All of these features can be managed through the “Manage Text and Push Alerts” page in the Discover Mobile App or through your device-level settings on your mobile device.</string>
    <string name="use_of_push_text_2">In order to access the Push Alerts, you will need to: (a) have a mobile device that is capable of receiving push notifications and running an iOS or Android operating system; (b) download the latest version on the Discover Mobile App; (c) register with Discover.com and create a user-id and password; (d) enable push notifications in your mobile device settings; (e) login to the Discover Mobile App and select what Push Alerts you would like to  receive; and (f) save these settings and agree to these Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="use_of_push_text_3">It is your responsibility to determine if your mobile service provider supports Push Alerts and your mobile device is capable of receiving Push Alerts. Our Push Alerts are subject to the terms and conditions of your agreement(s) with your mobile device carrier. You are responsible for any fees imposed by your mobile device carrier of any kind whatsoever. You acknowledge that our Push Alerts are sent to you without being encrypted and will include information pertaining to your Account, although we will not include your complete account number or social security number in any unencrypted text.</string>
    <string name="use_of_push_text_4">You can un-enroll to receive Push Alerts at any time by logging into your Discover Mobile App and deselecting the Push Alerts you no longer wish to receive.  You can also turn off push notifications on your mobile device.</string>
    <string name="usage_period_header">Usage Period</string>
    <string name="usage_period_text">Your right to access and use the Text Messages and Push Alerts will commence on the date you first click on an acceptance button or otherwise access the Text Messages or Push Alerts (“Usage”).  During Usage, you will have access to all of the available features of the Text Messages and Push Alerts for which you have enrolled.  At the end of the Usage period, defined as unenrollment or disabling of Text Messages or Push Alerts, your right to access the Text Messages or Push Alerts and any licenses granted in connection therewith will automatically be terminated.</string>
    <string name="ownership_header">Ownership of Intellectual Property and Limited License</string>
    <string name="ownership_text_1">The Text Messages and Push Alerts includes certain proprietary content and other materials, including, without limitation, the DFS logo, and all designs, text, graphics, pictures, information, data, software, sound files, other files and the selection and arrangement thereof (collectively, the “Materials“).  All copyrights, patents, trademarks, trade secrets and/or any other intellectual property rights related to the Text Messages, Push Alerts or the Materials (collectively, “Intellectual Property“) are and will remain the sole property of DFS or its licensors and are protected by U.S. and international law.  Other than the limited license expressly set forth in this Section, you do not acquire any title or ownership rights in the Intellectual Property.  You acknowledge that DFS considers the Intellectual Property to contain trade secrets of DFS and/or its licensors.  Such trade secrets include, without limitation, the software, the specific design, structure and logic of individual programs, their interactions with other portions of programs, both internal and external, and the programming techniques employed therein.</string>
    <string name="ownership_text_2">You are granted a limited, non-sublicensable, revocable, royalty-free and non-transferable license to access and use the Text Messages, Push Alerts and Materials during the Usage period subject to these Terms of Use and does not include: (a) any resale or commercial use of the Text Messages, Push Alerts or the Materials; (b) the distribution, public performance or public display of any Materials; (c) modifying or otherwise making any derivative uses of the Text Messages, Push Alerts or Materials, or any portion thereof; (d) use of any data mining, robots or similar data gathering or extraction methods; (e) downloading (other than the page caching) of any portion of the Text Messages, Push Alerts, the Materials or any information contained therein, except as expressly permitted on the Text Messages or Push Alerts; or (f) any use of the Text Messages, Push Alerts or the Materials other than for its intended purpose.  Any use of the Text Messages, Push Alerts or the Materials other than as specifically authorized herein, without the prior written permission of DFS, is strictly prohibited and will terminate the license granted herein.  Such unauthorized use may also violate applicable laws including without limitation copyright, patent and trademark laws and applicable communications regulations and statutes.</string>
    <string name="privacy_header">Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_text_2">DFS or third parties under contract with DFS may collect information from your mobile device. This information is generally used to help us deliver the most relevant information to you. Examples of information that may be collected include, but are not limited to: device id, OS platform, OS version, mobile phone number, and wireless carrier. This information is used for the sending and receiving of Text Messages and Push Alerts and troubleshooting issues that may arise. Third parties have agreed not to use the information they collect from your device except to deliver information to you on our behalf. In order to no longer have the information described above collected, you may completely uninstall the Discover application from your mobile device and unenroll from Text Messages.</string>
    <string name="privacy_text_1">DFS collects, uses and discloses personally identifiable information from its users consistent with its Privacy Policy, located at https://www.discover.com/credit-cards/help-center/account/privacy-policies/index.html.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">The Text Messages and Push Alerts are provided as a convenience to you for information purposes only. You acknowledge that our Text Messages and Push Alerts are sent to you without being encrypted and will include information pertaining to your Account.  The information on the Text Messages and Push Alerts is provided on an "AS IS," and "AS AVAILABLE" basis. DFS does not warrant the information provided herein or your use of our Text Messages and Push Alerts generally, either expressly or impliedly, for any particular purpose and expressly disclaims any implied warranties, including but not limited to, warranties of title, non-infringement, merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. DFS does not represent or warrant that the Text Messages and Push Alerts are compatible with any hardware or software versions or applications (including any specific versions of your phone, tablet, computer, or its specific operating system).   DFS will not be responsible for any loss or damage that could result from interception by third parties of any information made available to you via our Text Messages or Push Alerts. DFS cannot and does not guarantee the accuracy, validity, timeliness or completeness of any information or data made available to you for any particular purpose. Neither DFS, nor any of its affiliates, directors, officers or employees, nor any third party vendor, will be liable or have any responsibility of any kind for any loss or damage that you incur in the event of any failure or interruption of our Text Messages or Push Alerts, or resulting from the act or omission of any other party involved in providing Text Messages or Push Alerts, or from any other cause relating to your access to, inability to access, or use of the Text Messages or Push Alerts, whether or not the circumstances giving rise to such cause may have been within the control of DFS or of any vendor providing software or services. In no event will DFS or any such parties be liable to you, whether in contract or tort, for any direct, special, indirect, consequential or incidental damages or any other damages of any kind even if DFS or any other such party has been advised of the possibility thereof. This limitation on liability includes, but is not limited to, the transmission of any viruses which may infect a user\'s equipment, failure of mechanical or electronic equipment or communication lines, telephone or other interconnect problems unauthorized access, theft, operator errors, strikes or other labor problems or any force majeure. DFS cannot and does not guarantee continuous, uninterrupted or secure Text Message or Push Alerts service.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_header">Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability</string>
    <string name="indemnification_header">Indemnification</string>
    <string name="indemnification_text">You shall indemnify, and hold harmless, and upon DFS’ request, defend, DFS, its independent contractors, service providers and consultants, and their respective past, present, and future officers, directors, agents and employees from any and all claims, damages, losses, liabilities, costs, settlement fees and expenses including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys’ fees and costs incurred directly or indirectly by DFS arising from or related to any of the following: (i) your use of or inability to use the Text Messages or Push Alerts; (ii) your violation of these Terms of Use; (iii) your violation of any rights of another; or (iv) your conduct in connection with the Text Messages or Push Alerts.</string>
    <string name="service_modification_header">Modifications to the Service</string>
    <string name="service_modification_text">DFS reserves the right, in its sole discretion, without any obligation and without any notice requirement, to change, improve or correct the Text Messages or Push Alerts and to suspend the Text Messages or Push Alerts for scheduled or unscheduled maintenance, upgrades, improvements or corrections. DFS may discontinue or change Push Alerts at any time without prior notice to you, subject to applicable law. You agree that DFS will not be liable for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Text Messages or Push Alerts, or any part thereof. Sections 4 through 10 shall survive the expiration or termination of these Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="change_terms_header">Change to Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="change_terms_text">DFS reserves the right to change or modify these Terms of Use at any time and in its sole discretion.  Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting of the revised Terms of Use and you waive any right you may have to receive specific notice of such changes or modifications unless required by applicable law.  Your continued use of Text Messages and Push Alerts following the posting of changes or modifications will confirm your acceptance of such changes or modifications.  Therefore, you should frequently review the Terms and applicable policies to understand the terms and conditions that apply to your use of Text Messages and Push Alerts.  If you do not agree to the amended terms, you must stop using the Text Messages and Push Alerts.</string>
    <string name="misc_header">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="mis_text_1">These Terms of Use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Illinois, without regard to conflicts of laws provisions. Sole and exclusive jurisdiction for any action or proceeding arising out of or related to these Terms of Use shall be in an appropriate state or federal court located in the County of Lake, State of Illinois and the parties unconditionally waive their respective rights to a jury trial. Any cause of action you may have with respect to your use of Text Messages or Push Alerts must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of these Terms of Use, or a portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to affect the intent of these Terms of Use, and the remainder of these Terms of Use shall continue in full force and effect. These Terms of Use constitutes the entire agreement between DFS and you with respect to Text Messages and Push Alerts and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications, agreements and understandings between DFS and you with respect to the subject matter hereof. These Terms of Use do not alter in any way the terms of conditions of any other agreement you may have with DFS, or its subsidiaries or affiliates, for products, services or otherwise.</string>
    <string name="mis_text_2">These Terms of Use were last updated September 13, 2012. Please check back for updates and changes.</string>
    <string name="or_more">or more</string>
    <string name="minimum_amount_is">Minimum amount is </string>
    <string name="of_your_credit_line">of your credit line</string>
    <string name="hypen">-</string>
    <string name="plus">+</string>
    <string name="exclamation">!</string>
    
    <string-array name="manage_you_accounts_categories">
        <item>STMT</item>
        <item>MINP</item>
        <item>PMTR</item>
        <item>MCRD</item>
        <item>BALT</item>
        <item>FRAD</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="manage_your_accounts_headers">
        <item>Statement Available</item>
	    <item>Minimum Payment</item>
	    <item>Payment Posted</item>
	    <item>Merchant Refund Posted</item>
	    <item>Balance Transfer Posted</item>
	    <item>Fraud Alert</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="manage_your_accounts_text">
        <item>Notify me when a new statement is available to view.</item>
	    <item>Get a reminder before your payment is due if the minimum amount has not been received.</item>
	    <item>Know exactly when your payments are posted.</item>
	    <item>Know when a merchant refund/credit is posted.</item>
	    <item>Know when a balance transfer is posted.</item>
	    <item>Be immediately notified if we detect any unusual activity.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="purchase_amount_category">TAMT</string>
    <string name="balance_amount_category">BALA</string>
    <string name="credit_line_ammount_category">CRLT</string>
    
    <string name="purchase_amount_header">Account purchase exceeds a specified amount:</string>
    <string name="balance_amount_header">Account balance exceeds a specified amount:</string>
    <string name="credit_line_ammount_header">Nearing account credit line:</string>

	<string name="credit_line_ammount_text">Learn when your account balance is within</string>
    
	<string name="rewards_reminder_category">5CBB</string>
	<string name="rewards_reminder_header">Rewards Reminder</string>
	<string name="rewards_reminder_text">Learn when it\'s time to enroll for a Rewards Program</string>
	
	<string name="cashback_bonus_category">MRRW</string>
	<string name="cashback_bonus_header">Cashback Bonus Reaches Specified Amount</string>

    
    <string name="history_title">History</string>
    <string name="manage">Manage</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="older_alerts">Alerts over 45 days old will be automatically deleted.</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
</resources>