<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="customer_service">
        Customer Service
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_and_security">
        Privacy &amp; Security
    </string>
    <string name="register_now">
        Register\nNow
    </string>
    <string name="forgot_id_or_pass_text">
        Forgot User ID/Password?
    </string>
    <string name="card">
        Card
    </string>
    <string name="bank">
        Bank
    </string>
    <string name="go_to">
        Go to:
    </string>
    <string name="login_button_text">
        Secure Login
    </string>
    <string name="hide">
        Hide
    </string>
    <string name="show">
        Show
    </string>
    <string name="remember_user_id">
        Remember User ID
    </string>
    <string name="password">
        Password
    </string>
    <string name="user_id">
        User ID
    </string>
    <string name="vertical_separator">
        |
    </string>
    <string name="logout_sucess">
        You are now logged out. Thank you for using Discover Mobile.
    </string>
    <string name="session_expired">
        Your login session has expired.
    </string>
<!--  LOGIN ERRORS -->
	<string name="id_invalid">
	    Please check your ID and try again.
	</string>
	<string name="pass_invalid">
	    Please check your password and try again.
	</string>
	<string name="account_number_reregistered">
	    We\'re sorry, you may no longer use this Discover card account number to access Discover.com Mobile. 
	    Instead, please visit www.discover.com to create a User ID and password. If you have any questions, 
	    please contact Customer Service at 
		<a href='tel:18777427822'>1&#8211;877&#8211;742&#8211;7822</a> .
	</string>
	<string name="account_setup_pending">
	    Your online access is still being set up. Please try back again later.
	</string>
	<string name="account_number_changed">
	    Your Discover Card Account Number has been changed. In order to access your account through the 
	    mobile channel, you must first log in to the Account Center on www.discover.com. For more information, 
	    please contact Customer Service at 
	    <a href='tel:18777427822'>1&#8211;877&#8211;742&#8211;7822</a>
	</string>
	<string name="internal_server_error_500">
	    <h3>Discover.com Mobile Error</h3>We\'re sorry. Your request cannot be completed at this time. 
	    We sincerely apologize for this inconvenience and are working to resolve this issue soon.
	     For further assistance please call 
	     <a href='tel:18777427822'>1&#8211;877&#8211;742&#8211;7822</a>
	</string>
	<string name="internal_server_error_503">
	    We\'re sorry. Our services are unavailable at this time. <br/>We apologize for any inconvenience.
	</string>
	<string name="forbidden_403">
	    The request has been understood but has been refused due to incompatible client version.
	</string>
	<string name="temporary_outage">
	    <h3>We\'re sorry.</h3><br/>Some of our web site features are unavailable at this time. 
	    We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.
	</string>
	<string name="planned_outage_one">
	    We\'re sorry. We will be performing a system maintenance between 1 a.m. and 6 a.m. Eastern Time.
	     We apologize for any inconvenience. Please try again later, or for immediate assistance call 
		 <a href='tel:18777427822'>1&#8211;877&#8211;742&#8211;7822</a>.
	</string>
	<string name="cashback_bonus_unavailable">
	    Cashback Bonus is currently unavailable. We apologize for the inconvenience. Please try again later.
	</string>
	<string name="no_data_found">
	    No data found.
	</string>
	<string name="contact_customer_service">
	    Contact Customer Service
	</string>
	<string name="not_primary_cardholder">
	    At this time, only the primary cardholder can register for and access Account Center.  
	    For more assistance, please contact Customer Service at 
		<a href='tel:18777427822'>1&#8211;877&#8211;742&#8211;7822</a>.
	</string>
	<string name="unscheduled_maintenance">
	    We\'re sorry. We are currently updating our system and cannot complete your request at this time. 
	    We apologize for any inconvenience. Please try again later or, for immediate assistance call 
	    <a href='tel:18003472683'>1&#8211;800&#8211;347&#8211;2683</a>.
	</string>
	<string name="locked_account">
	    For security purposes, your online account has been locked.<br/>Please call Discover
	         Customer Service at 
	         <a href='tel:18882518003'>1&#8211;888&#8211;251&#8211;8003</a> 
	         for information about accessing your account online.
	</string>
	<string name="cannot_save_account_number">
	    To protect the security of your Account, we do not save your Discover card Account number
	     with the "Remember My User ID" feature. It is only available when you use a user ID to log in.
	</string>
	<string name="atm_locator">
        ATM\nLocator
    </string>
	<string name="privacy_and_terms">
        Privacy &amp; Terms
    </string>
</resources>