<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string-array name="card_push_text_faq_array">
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_one</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_one</item>
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_two</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_two</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_three</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_three</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_four</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_four</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_five</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_five</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_six</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_six</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_seven</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_seven</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_eight</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_eight</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_nine</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_nine</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_ten</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_ten</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_push_text_title_eleven</item>
        <item>@string/card_push_text_content_eleven</item>  
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_one">What is a Push Alert?</string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_one">
        A push alert is a message sent from the Discover Mobile App to your mobile device informing you when new account 
        information becomes available. Depending on your device settings, these alerts can display in the form of badges, banners, 
        or alerts and be viewed again later on the “Push Alerts History” page. 
        You will only receive alerts for which you have enrolled. These subscriptions can be updated through the 
        “Manage Text and Push Alerts” page on the app. No fees are associated with Push Alerts.
    </string>
     
    <string name="card_push_text_title_two">How do I turn on/off Push Alerts?</string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_two">
		<![CDATA[Below are the ways to manage your Push Alerts:
		<br/>-From the left-hand navigation in the Discover App, under Profile &amp; Settings, select “Manage Text &amp; Alerts.” Then select the Push Alerts you would like to activate/deactivate and save your changes.
		<br/>-To turn on/off all Push Alerts, slide the "Enable Push Alerts" switch from ON to OFF and vice versa, on the 
		“Manage Text &amp; Alerts” page and save your changes.
		<br/>-Push Alerts also can be turned off/on via your mobile device settings. To turn on/off notifications on your device, go to the notification center in the device settings and locate the Discover Mobile App icon. Click the icon and a screen will open. Choose the option to turn off/on Push Alerts.
   
		<br/><br/><b>Note:</b> If you disable Discover Push Alerts from your mobile device settings you will not be able to change your 
		Push Alerts settings in the Discover Mobile App until you turn the Discover Push Alerts back on in device settings.]]>
	</string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_three">I activated Push Alerts. Why have I not received any? </string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_three">
        Check to make sure Discover Push Alerts are enabled in your mobile device settings. To turn on notifications on your 
        mobile device, go to the notification center in the device settings and locate the Discover Mobile App icon. 
        Click the icon and a screen will open. Choose the option to turn on Push Alerts.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_four">What is the difference between Text Alerts and Push Alerts?</string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_four">
        <![CDATA[Text Messages are available for all devices with text message receiving capabilities while Push Alerts are sent directly through the Discover Mobile App. 
		<br/><br/><b>Note:</b> Text charges vary by carrier and plan. Please contact your service provider to find out if your plan has fees for receiving text messages.]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_five">How do I enroll in Text Messages?</string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_five">
        <![CDATA[To enroll in text messages, from the left-hand navigation in the Discover App, under Profile &amp; Settings, 
        select “Manage Text &amp; Alerts” and choose the text message you would like to receive. Once you have chosen your alerts, 
        you will be asked to verify or provide your mobile phone number and carrier information. Enter or verify the information 
        and then save your settings. You will then receive an opt-in text message from “DISCOV (347268).” 
        You must text back “YES” along with the last 4 digits of your account to complete your enrollment.

		<br/><br/>You can also enroll in text messages on Discover.com under Account Profile and Preferences.]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_six">What Text Messages will Discover send me? </string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_six">
        You will only receive text messages for which you have enrolled. 
        You can elect to enroll in a number of text message reminders including when statements are available, 
        when your payment has posted, and when your payment is due. 
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_seven">Can I receive fraud alerts via Text Message?</string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_seven">
        <![CDATA[Yes. You can sign up to receive fraud alerts that will notify you when unusual activity is suspected in your account, 
        a transaction exceeds your charge limit, and if your account is approaching its credit limit. 
        To enroll, select “Manage Text &amp; Alerts,” under Profile &amp; Settings, 
        from the left-hand navigation in the Discover app and select the box next to “Fraud Alert.”

		<br/><br/>You can also sign up for this alert on discover.com under Account Profile and Preferences.]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_eight">How do I stop receiving Text Messages from Discover?</string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_eight">
        <![CDATA[Below are the ways to manage your Text Alerts:
		<br/><br/>&#8226;On the “Manage Text &amp; Alerts” page in the Discover App, select the text messages you would like to activate/deactivate and save your changes.
		<br/><br/>&#8226;To unsubscribe from all text messages, text "STOP ALL" to DISCOV (347268).
		<br/><br/>&#8226;Update your text message enrollments on Discover.com via your Account Profile.]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_nine">I signed up to receive several text alerts. Why have I not received any?</string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_nine">
       You may need to confirm the mobile number and carrier are entered correctly on the “Manage Text &amp; Alerts” page in the 
       Discover App or under Account Profile and Preferences on Discover.com. You should also check to see if you have selected 
       the text messages you would like to receive from the “Manage Text &amp; Alerts” page and resend “YES” along with the last 4 
       digits of your accounts to DISCOV (347268) to ensure you are opted in for the alerts. If the above options still don’t 
       work, please call Discover web support at 1-877-742-7822 or contact your mobile carrier to 
       make sure you are able to receive text messages.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_ten">Can I contact Discover Card via text message? </string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_ten">
        Discover does not provide two-way communication with its customers through text messaging at this time. 
        If you would like to stop receiving reminders, reply "STOP" from the most recent text message reminder you received.  
        If you still continue to receive text messages after your have replied, please contact Discover web support at 1-877-742-7822
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_push_text_title_eleven">Are text message reminders secure? </string>
    <string name="card_push_text_content_eleven">
        Text message reminders are protected by Discover, and we will never include your password or 
        full account information in the message. 
    </string>
    
</resources>