<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- ATM Locator FAQ String Array -->
    <string-array name="atm_locator_faq_array">
        <item>@string/how_to_find_atm_title</item>
        <item>@string/how_to_find_atm_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/surcharge_free_title</item>
        <item>@string/surcharge_free_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/are_there_fees_title</item>
        <item>@string/are_there_fees_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/where_can_you_use_title</item>
        <item>@string/where_can_you_use_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/lost_or_stolen_title</item>
        <item>@string/lost_or_stolen_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/how_change_pin_title</item>
        <item>@string/how_change_pin_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/daily_withdrawal_limit_title</item>
        <item>@string/daily_withdrawal_limit_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/atm_withdrawal_fees_title</item>
        <item>@string/atm_withdrawal_fees_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/outside_us_use_title</item>
        <item>@string/outside_us_use_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/deposit_to_atm_title</item>
        <item>@string/deposit_to_atm_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/wrongfully_charged_title</item>
        <item>@string/wrongfully_charged_body</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <!-- ATM Locator FAQ Strings -->
    <string name="how_to_find_atm_title">How do I find an ATM near me?</string>
	<string name="how_to_find_atm_body">
	    To find an ATM near you, click the “Search” icon at the top of the ATM Locator screen and type in the address, 
	    zip code, or landmark where you wish to find an ATM.
	</string>
	
	<string name="surcharge_free_title">
	    How do I find a surcharge-free ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="surcharge_free_body">
	    To display only surcharge-free ATMs on your search, enable the “Display only Surcharge-Free ATMs” button. 
	    Surcharge-free ATMs are represented by orange icons in map and list view.
	</string>
	
	<string name="are_there_fees_title">
	    Are there any fees associated with the use of a surcharge-free ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="are_there_fees_body">
	    You will not be charged an ATM surcharge when you withdraw cash with your Discover debit card at the 
	    surcharge-free ATMs represented by orange map pins. If you take a cash advance with your Discover 
	    credit card at one of these locations, you will not be charged an ATM surcharge fee but your cash advance 
	    APR and cash advance fee will apply.  ATM surcharge fees may apply to Discover cash withdrawals at 
	    other ATMs not designated “Surcharge-Free.”
	</string>
	
	<string name="where_can_you_use_title">
	    At which ATMs can I use my Discover debit card?
	</string>
	<string name="where_can_you_use_body">
	    You can use your Discover debit card at ATMs displaying the Discover, PULSE® or MoneyPass® logos.
	</string>
	
	<string name="lost_or_stolen_title">
	    How do I report a lost or stolen debit card?
	</string>
	<string name="lost_or_stolen_body">
	    To report lost or stolen debit cards, please call 1-800-347-7000 immediately. 
	</string>
	
	<string name="how_change_pin_title">
	    How do I change my PIN?
	</string>
	<string name="how_change_pin_body">
	    To change your PIN, please call 1-800-983-1266; you will be prompted to enter your current 
	    PIN and then your new desired PIN.
	</string>
	
	<string name="daily_withdrawal_limit_title">
	    Is there a daily ATM withdrawal limit?
	</string>
	<string name="daily_withdrawal_limit_body">
	    Yes. The maximum amount you can withdraw from ATMs is $510.00 per day. 
	    The Discover ATM withdrawal limit is $510 per day. 
	    Some ATMs may have lower withdrawal limits but you complete multiple transactions until you meet the 
	    Discover withdrawal limit of $510 per day. 
	</string>
	
	<string name="atm_withdrawal_fees_title">
	    Are there any fees for withdrawing money from an ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="atm_withdrawal_fees_body">
	    There are no fees for withdrawing money from 23,000 surcharge-free MoneyPass ATMs nationwide. 
	    However, you may be subject to a fee from the ATM owner/financial institution if you do not use a 
	    surcharge-free ATM. Discover will never charge you a fee to use an ATM. 
	    You can use our ATM Locator to find surcharge-free MoneyPass ATMs nearby.
	</string>
	
	<string name="outside_us_use_title">
	    Can I use my debit card outside of the United States? 
	</string>
	<string name="outside_us_use_body">
	    You can use your Discover debit card to withdraw cash at ATMs and make purchases at 
	    participating merchants in the United States, Canada, Mexico and the Caribbean wherever you see the 
	    PULSE®, Discover, or MoneyPass® symbols. 
	</string>
	
	<string name="deposit_to_atm_title">
	    Can I make a deposit at an ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="deposit_to_atm_body">
	    Currently, Discover Bank does not accept deposits at ATM locations 
	    (other than at its branch in Greenwood, DE), If you need to deposit a check, please use the mobile 
	    check deposit feature on Discover’s mobile app or mail it to us at \n
		Discover Bank\n
		P.O. Box 30417\n
		Salt Lake City, UT\n
		84130
	</string>
	
	<string name="wrongfully_charged_title">
	    I was charged a fee for using my debit card at an ATM that I believed to be a surcharge-free ATM. 
	    What can I do? 
	</string>
	<string name="wrongfully_charged_body">
	    If you are at a MoneyPass ATM and it indicates you are being charged a fee, accept the fee and proceed with 
	    your transaction. Then notify Discover Bank by sending a message through our Secure Message Center or 
	    calling us at 1-800-347-7000 and we will credit your account for fee if you provide the following information:\n 
		•	Date and time of the transaction\n
		•	ATM location\n
		•	Last four digits of your debit card\n
		•	Amount of the fee you were charged\n
	</string>
</resources>
