<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string-array name="card_send_money_faq_array">
        <item>@string/card_send_money_title_one</item>
        <item>@string/card_send_money_content_one</item>
        
        <item>@string/card_send_money_title_two</item>
        <item>@string/card_send_money_content_two</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_send_money_title_three</item>
        <item>@string/card_send_money_content_three</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_send_money_title_four</item>
        <item>@string/card_send_money_content_four</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_send_money_title_five</item>
        <item>@string/card_send_money_content_five</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_send_money_title_six</item>
        <item>@string/card_send_money_content_six</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_send_money_title_seven</item>
        <item>@string/card_send_money_content_seven</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_send_money_title_eight</item>
        <item>@string/card_send_money_content_eight</item>  
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="card_send_money_title_one">What is Money Messenger?</string>
    <string name="card_send_money_content_one">
        Money Messenger is a service powered by PayPal Inc. that lets you send money to just about anyone using your computer or mobile phone if your account is eligible.
    </string>
     
    <string name="card_send_money_title_two">How does Discover Money Messenger work?</string>
    <string name="card_send_money_content_two">
        If your account is eligible, you can send money to anyone with an email address or mobile phone number. 
        PayPal sends a message to the recipient letting them know their money is ready. 
        The recipient signs into their PayPal account to receive the money. 
        If they don’t have a PayPal account, all they need to do is sign up for one. 
        The amount you send is charged to your Discover card account just like a normal purchase.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_send_money_title_three">Are there any fees to send money through Discover Money Messenger?</string>
    <string name="card_send_money_content_three">
        There are no fees for you to send money and the amount will be charged to your Discover card account as a regular 
        purchase. If you are sending money to friends or family, there are no fees charged to them to accept the money. 
        If you are sending money to a business for goods or services, PayPal will charge them a fee to accept the money.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_send_money_title_four">Do I need a PayPal account to send money?</string>
    <string name="card_send_money_content_four">
        No, you do not need a PayPal account to send money. 
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_send_money_title_five">Does the person I’m sending money to need to be a Discover Cardmember?</string>
    <string name="card_send_money_content_five">
        No, the person receiving the money doesn’t need to be a Discover cardmember. However, they will need to sign up for a 
        PayPal account, if they don’t already have one, in order to claim their money. When PayPal notifies the recipient you have
         sent them money, they will receive instructions on how to open up a PayPal account to access it.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_send_money_title_six">Does the person I’m sending money to need a PayPal account?</string>
    <string name="card_send_money_content_six">
        You can send money to anyone even if they don’t yet have a PayPal account. 
        But, the recipient must sign up for an account at PayPal.com in order to claim their money. 
        When PayPal notifies the recipient that you have sent them money, 
        they will also receive simple instructions on how to open up a PayPal account to access it. 
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_send_money_title_seven">How does the recipient actually get the money?</string>
    <string name="card_send_money_content_seven">
       	PayPal sends a message via email or text message to the recipient letting them know their money is ready. 
       	If they are a registered PayPal account holder, the money is instantly deposited into their account. 
       	If the recipient is new to PayPal, they simply open an account, link their email address or mobile number 
       	and they will have immediate access to the money. After they log in to PayPal, 
       	they have the option to spend the money online at any merchant that accepts PayPal, 
       	transfer it to a bank account, or request a check.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_send_money_title_eight">Can anyone use Money Messenger?</string>
    <string name="card_send_money_content_eight">
        You must be a Discover cardmember with an eligible account and be registered for the Account Center on Discover.com to 
        use this service. Business and Titanium cards are currently not eligible to use Money Messenger.
    </string>
  
</resources>