<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <!-- Check Deposit FAQ String Array -->
    <string-array name="check_deposit_faq_array">
        <item>@string/how_to_access_deposit_title</item>
        <item>@string/how_to_access_deposit_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/kinds_of_checks_title</item>
        <item>@string/kinds_of_checks_body</item>
               
        <item>@string/deposit_limits_title</item>
        <item>@string/deposit_limits_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/when_deposit_posted_title</item>
        <item>@string/when_deposit_posted_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/deposit_available_title</item>
        <item>@string/deposit_available_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/check_care_title</item>
        <item>@string/check_care_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/deposit_fees_title</item>
        <item>@string/deposit_fees_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/check_rejected_title</item>
        <item>@string/check_rejected_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/check_exceeds_limit_title</item>
        <item>@string/check_exceeds_limit_body</item>
        
    </string-array>
    
    <!-- Check Deposit FAQ String Values -->
    <string name="how_to_access_deposit_title">
        How do I access the Mobile Check Deposit service?
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_access_deposit_body">
        You must already be enrolled in the Discover Account Center. 
        Once enrolled, you can download the Discover App from your App store to your Smartphone. 
        Log into the Discover App and click on the Check Deposit tab. 
        Follow the simple instructions to submit your check deposit.
    </string>
    
    <string name="kinds_of_checks_title">
        What kind of checks can I deposit with this service?
    </string>
    <string name="kinds_of_checks_body">
        Checks payable to you, in U.S. dollars and drawn on any U.S. bank including, but not limited to the 
        following:\nPersonal checks\nBusiness checks\nUS Treasury checks
    </string>
    
    <string name="deposit_limits_title">
        Are there deposit limits?
    </string>
    <string name="deposit_limits_body">
        You may deposit up to 50 checks per day.
		\n\nFor savings and money market accounts, there is a limit of $5,000 per check, $25,000 per month.
		\n\nFor checking accounts, there is a limit of $1,000 per check, $5,000 per day and $15,000 per month.
		\n\nAccounts that have been open for less than 6 months may have reduced limits.
    </string>
    
    <string name="deposit_fees_title">
		Are there any fees to use the Mobile Check deposit service?
	</string>
    <string name="deposit_fees_body">
        No. There are no fees to use this service. Message and data rates may apply. 
    </string>

    <string name="when_deposit_posted_title">
        When will my deposit be posted to my account?
    </string>
    <string name="when_deposit_posted_body">
        Deposits received and accepted by 6:30 P.M. Eastern Time on a business day will be posted to your 
        account on that day. Deposits received and accepted after this time will be posted the following business day.
    </string>
    
    <string name="deposit_available_title">
        When will my deposit be available for withdrawal?
    </string>
    
    <string name="deposit_available_body">
        For savings and money market accounts the funds will be available 
        the 5th business day after the day of deposit.
		\n\nFor checking accounts, $200 will be available the next day, the remainder the 2nd business day after the 
		day of deposit. For new customers for the first 30 days, $200 will be available the next day, the remainder 
		the 7th business day after the day of deposit. 
    </string>
    
    <string name="check_care_title">
        What should I do with my check after I deposit it?
    </string>
    <string name="check_care_body">
		After your deposit has been credited to your account, 
		mark it void and store it in a secure location for 90 days.
    </string>
    
    <string name="check_rejected_title">
        What if my check deposit is rejected?
    </string>
    <string name="check_rejected_body">
       If your check is rejected, you will receive a notification via e-mail. 
       You may log into the Account Center for a secure message that will provide the reason the check was rejected.
    </string>
    
    <string name="check_exceeds_limit_title">
		What if my check amount exceeds the deposit limit?
    </string>
    <string name="check_exceeds_limit_body">
		Mail the check that includes your account number, made payable to you or Discover Bank to: 
		\n\nDiscover Bank
		\nPO Box 30417
		\nSalt Lake City, UT 84130
    </string>
    
</resources>
