<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Online Bill Pay Array -->
		<string-array name="online_bill_pay_array">
		    <item>@string/who_can_use_bill_pay_title</item>
		    <item>@string/who_can_use_bill_pay_body</item>
		    
		    <item>@string/who_can_i_pay_title</item>
		    <item>@string/who_can_i_pay_body</item>
		    
		    <item>@string/fees_associated_title</item>
		    <item>@string/fees_associated_body</item>
		    
		    <item>@string/how_is_payment_sent_title</item>
		    <item>@string/how_is_payment_sent_body</item>
		    
		    <item>@string/when_payment_sent_title</item>
		    <item>@string/when_payment_sent_body</item>
		    
		    <item>@string/status_question_title</item>
		    <item>@string/status_question_body</item>
		    
		    <item>@string/delete_payment_title</item>
		    <item>@string/delete_payment_body</item>
		    
		    <item>@string/repeating_payment_title</item>
		    <item>@string/repeating_payment_body</item>
		</string-array>
	
	<!-- Online Bill Pay Items -->
		<string name="who_can_use_bill_pay_title">
		    Who can use Online Bill Pay?
		</string>
		<string name="who_can_use_bill_pay_body">
		    Online Bill Pay can be used by any Discover Bank customer who has a Money Market Account, 
		    with the exception of individuals acting in the following capacities: Agent, Attorney-In-Fact and Guardian.
		</string>
		
		<string name="who_can_i_pay_title">Who can I pay?</string>
		<string name="who_can_i_pay_body">
			Use Online Bill Pay for your utilities, credit card payments, insurance premiums or other companies 
			you make regular payments to. You can also pay other individuals and businesses, 
			such as landlords, contractors, relatives, etc.
		</string>
		
		<string name="fees_associated_title">Are there any fees associated with Online Bill Pay?</string>
		<string name="fees_associated_body">
			No. Our Online Bill Pay service is offered at no charge. However, bill pay transactions count 
			toward the limit of 6 restricted withdrawals from your Money Market Account per statement cycle. 
			For more information, please refer to your Account Agreement.
		</string>
		
		<string name="how_is_payment_sent_title">
		    How will my bill payment be sent?
		</string>
		<string name="how_is_payment_sent_body">
		    Bill payments are sent electronically or by check through the mail to your payee. 
		    And we guarantee that your bill payment will reach your payee by the Deliver By date.
		</string>
		
		<string name="when_payment_sent_title">
		    When will my account be debited for my bill payment?
		</string>
		<string name="when_payment_sent_body">
		    For bill payments sent electronically, the funds will be debited on the Deliver By date. 
		    For bill payments made by check, the funds will be debited when the payee has cashed the check.
		</string>
		
		<string name="status_question_title">
		    What does the Status next to my bill payment mean?
		</string>
		<string name="status_question_body">
		    Scheduled – Bill payment has been scheduled but not yet initiated. Bill payments in a 
		    Scheduled status can be edited or deleted.\n\nProcessing – Bill payment has been initiated and 
		    is in the process of being paid. 
			These bill payments cannot be edited or deleted.\n\nSent – Bill payment has been sent to the 
			payee.\n\nPaid – Electronic bill payments are marked at Paid when the
			payment has been sent. In the case of a paper check being mailed, 
			bill payments are marked as Paid 3 business days thereafter.\n\nCancelled –
			Bill payment has been cancelled. Deleting a scheduled bill
			payment will result in a cancelled status.
		</string>
		
		<string name="delete_payment_title">Why can’t I edit or delete a bill payment?</string>
		<string name="delete_payment_body">
		    If the bill payment has already been processed and sent to the payee, you cannot edit or delete it. 
		    Additionally, bill payments that have been scheduled by a Joint Account holder can only be edited or 
		    deleted by the person who initially scheduled the bill payment.
		</string>
		
		<string name="repeating_payment_title">How do I set up a repeating bill payment?</string>
		<string name="repeating_payment_body">
		    To set up a repeating bill payment, visit the full site at DiscoverBank.com and click on the Make a 
		    Payment tab or use the browser on your mobile phone and then click the Full Site link at the bottom.
		</string>
		
</resources>
