<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <!-- Check Deposit FAQ String Array -->
    <string-array name="check_deposit_faq_array">
        <item>@string/how_to_access_deposit_title</item>
        <item>@string/how_to_access_deposit_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/no_smartphone_title</item>
        <item>@string/no_smartphone_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/how_to_access_title</item>
        <item>@string/how_to_access_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/kinds_of_checks_title</item>
        <item>@string/kinds_of_checks_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/deposit_limits_title</item>
        <item>@string/deposit_limits_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/when_deposit_posted_title</item>
        <item>@string/when_deposit_posted_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/when_deposit_withdrawal_available_title</item>
        <item>@string/when_deposit_withdrawal_available_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/check_care_title</item>
        <item>@string/check_care_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/deposit_fees_title</item>
        <item>@string/deposit_fees_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/check_rejected_title</item>
        <item>@string/check_rejected_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/check_exceeds_limit_title</item>
        <item>@string/check_exceeds_limit_body</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <!-- Check Deposit FAQ String Values -->
    <string name="how_to_access_deposit_title">
        How do I access the Mobile Check Deposit service?
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_access_deposit_body">
        You should download the latest version of the Discover Mobile App from the Apple® or 
        Android™ store to your smartphone.  You must already be enrolled in the Discover Bank Account 
        Center to log into the Mobile App.  After logging in, click on the Deposit Check tab at the bottom 
        of the screen.  After you agree to the terms of the Mobile Check Deposit User Agreement (initial use only), 
        follow the simple instruction to submit your check.
    </string>
    
    <string name="no_smartphone_title">
    	What if I don’t have an Apple® or Android™ smartphone
    </string>
    <string name="no_smartphone_body">
        Presently the Mobile Check Deposit service is only available on these brand smartphones.
    </string>
    
    <string name="how_to_access_title">
        How do I access a copy of the Mobile Check Deposit User Agreement?
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_access_body">
        Please log into Discover.com and click the Customer Service link, followed by the Banking link, 
        and then the Forms and Documents link.
    </string>
    
    <string name="kinds_of_checks_title">
        What kind of checks can I deposit with this service?
    </string>
    <string name="kinds_of_checks_body">
        Checks payable to you, in U.S. dollars and drawn on any U.S. bank located in the United 
        States, including, but not limited to the follow: personal checks, checks from a business and 
        U.S. Treasury checks.
    </string>
    
    <string name="deposit_limits_title">
        Are there deposit limits?
    </string>
    <string name="deposit_limits_body">
        You may deposit up to 5 checks per day and 25 checks per month.  For saving and money market accounts, 
        there is a limit of $5,000 per check, $25,000 per day and $125,000 per month.
		\n\nFor checking accounts, there is a limit of $1,000 per check, $5,000 per day and $25,000 per month 
    </string>
    
    <string name="when_deposit_posted_title">
        When will my deposit be posted to my account?
    </string>
    <string name="when_deposit_posted_body">
        Deposits received and accepted by 6:30 P.M. Eastern Time on a business day will be posted to your account 
        on the next business day.  Deposits received and accepted after this time 
        will be posted to your account on the second business day.
    </string>
    
    <string name="when_deposit_withdrawal_available_title">
        When will my deposit be available for withdrawal?
    </string>
    <string name="when_deposit_withdrawal_available_body">
        For savings and money market accounts the funds will be available the 5th business day after the day of deposit.
        \n\nFor checking accounts, $200 will be available the next business day, 
		the remainder the 2nd business day after the day of deposit.
    </string>
    
    <string name="check_care_title">
        What should I do with my check after I deposit it?
    </string>
    <string name="check_care_body">
        After your deposit has been credited to your account, mark it void and store it in a secure location for 60 days.
    </string>
    
    <string name="deposit_fees_title">
        Are there any fees to use the Mobile Check Deposit service?
    </string>
    <string name="deposit_fees_body">
        No.  There are no feeds charged by Discover to use this service. 
        Message and data rates from your cellular service provider may apply.
    </string>
    
    <string name="check_rejected_title">
        What if my check deposit is rejected?
    </string>
    <string name="check_rejected_body">
        If your check is rejected, you will receive a notification via email. 
        You may log into the Account Center for a secure message that will provide the reason the check was rejected.
        \n\nIf you have any questions about a rejected deposit, you can call Discover at 866-245-7419.
    </string>
    
    <string name="check_exceeds_limit_title">
        What if my check amount exceeds one of the Mobile Check Deposit service limits?
    </string>
    <string name="check_exceeds_limit_body">
        Mail the endorsed check made payable to you or Discover Bank to the address below.  
        Include your account number on the check or include deposit instructions on a separate sheet of paper.
		\n\nDiscover Bank
		\nP.O. Box 30417
		\nSalt Lake City, UT 84130
    </string>
    
</resources>
