<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string-array name="card_refer_friend_faq_array">
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_title_one</item>
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_content_one</item>
        
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_title_two</item>
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_content_two</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_title_three</item>
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_content_three</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_title_four</item>
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_content_four</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_title_five</item>
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_content_five</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_title_six</item>
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_content_six</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_title_seven</item>
        <item>@string/card_refer_friend_content_seven</item>  
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="card_refer_friend_title_one">What\'s the Refer a Friend Program?</string>
    <string name="card_refer_friend_content_one">
        <![CDATA[It\'s an easy way to get an extra $50 in <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or 5,000 Miles. For each friend you refer who is approved for a 
        Discover card, you\'ll receive $50 in <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or 5,000 Miles. Once your friend makes their first purchase within the 
        first three months, they will also get $50 in <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or 5,000 Miles.
		
		<br/><br/>In order to participate, your account must be in good standing. To receive the $50 <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or 5,000 Miles 
		referral reward, your friend must apply for the specific offer you send and be approved. You will receive $50 Cashback 
		Bonus or 5,000 Miles for each approved friend, up to 10 new cardmembers per calendar year. Offer not available for 
		referrals that are existing Discover cardmembers. This offer is available online only. Individuals must apply for a 
		Discover card by December 31, 2013. You will not be notified whether a specific referral was approved or declined. 
		For email offers, your referral may not receive an email offer if they have previously opted out of receiving email 
		marketing communications from Discover or are an existing cardmember. Your friend who becomes a new cardmember will 
		also receive a $50 <i>Cashback Bonus</i> once they make a purchase within their first three months of account opening. 
		Please allow up to 5 weeks for <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or Miles to post to your account after each referral is approved for 
		their Discover card. The <i>Cashback Bonus</i> you receive may be taxable to you. Please contact your tax advisor.]]>
    </string>
     
    <string name="card_refer_friend_title_two">How can I refer a friend?</string>
    <string name="card_refer_friend_content_two">
        <![CDATA[From the left hand navigation, under Earn <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or Earn Miles, select “Refer a Friend”. 
        You can refer friends via email, Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. 
        We’ll handle everything, starting by sending a unique link to your friend so we can track the status of your referral.]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_refer_friend_title_three">What should I include in my referral?</string>
    <string name="card_refer_friend_content_three">
        You know your friends best. Tell them about all the great ways to use your Discover card and rewards that 
        you\'d think they\'d also enjoy by adding a personal message to your referral.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_refer_friend_title_four"><![CDATA[I\'ve already referred a friend; when will I receive my <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or Miles?]]></string>
    <string name="card_refer_friend_content_four">
        It may take up to 5 weeks for your $50 or 5,000 Miles to post to your account after each referral is approved. 
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_refer_friend_title_five">How many friends can I refer?</string>
    <string name="card_refer_friend_content_five">
        You will only earn rewards for the first 10 friends approved for a Discover card per calendar year; however, 
        there is no limit to how many friends you can refer.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_refer_friend_title_six">How much can I earn with the Refer a Friend program?</string>
    <string name="card_refer_friend_content_six">
        <![CDATA[You may earn up to $500 <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or 50,000 Miles per year.]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_refer_friend_title_seven"><![CDATA[Where can I check if I\'ve received my $50 <i>Cashback Bonus</i> or 5,000 Miles?]]></string>
    <string name="card_refer_friend_content_seven">
        <![CDATA[To view your Refer a Friend status, select “Refer a Friend” from the left-hand navigation under “Earn <i>Cashback Bonus</i>” or “Earn Miles” in the Discover App.]]>
    </string>
    
</resources>