<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- ATM Locator FAQ String Array -->
    <string-array name="atm_locator_faq_array">
        <item>@string/how_to_find_atm_title</item>
        <item>@string/how_to_find_atm_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/lost_or_stolen_title</item>
        <item>@string/lost_or_stolen_body</item>
                
        <item>@string/how_change_pin_title</item>
        <item>@string/how_change_pin_body</item>

        <item>@string/daily_withdrawal_limit_title</item>
        <item>@string/daily_withdrawal_limit_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/atm_withdrawal_fees_title</item>
        <item>@string/atm_withdrawal_fees_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/surcharge_free_title</item>
        <item>@string/surcharge_free_body</item>
	
        <item>@string/outside_us_use_title</item>
        <item>@string/outside_us_use_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/deposit_to_atm_title</item>
        <item>@string/deposit_to_atm_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/wrongfully_charged_title</item>
        <item>@string/wrongfully_charged_body</item>
        
        <item>@string/surcharge_free_fees_title</item>
        <item>@string/surcharge_free_fees_body</item>
        
    </string-array>
    
    <!-- ATM Locator FAQ Strings -->
    <string name="how_to_find_atm_title">How do I find an ATM near me?</string>
	<string name="how_to_find_atm_body">
	    Use our ATM Locator to find a nearby ATM, including free Allpoint&#174; and  MoneyPass&#174; ATMs.
	</string>
	
	<string name="surcharge_free_title">
	    How do I find a surcharge-free ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="surcharge_free_body">
	    To display only surcharge-free ATMs on your search, enable the “Display only Surcharge-Free ATMs” button. 
	    Surcharge-free ATMs are represented by orange icons in map and list view.
	</string>
	
	<string name="lost_or_stolen_title">
	    What happens if my debit card is lost or stolen?
	</string>
	<string name="lost_or_stolen_body">
		If your debit card is lost or stolen, call us at 1-800-347-7000 and a Banking Specialist will help you cancel your old card and order a new card. 
	</string>
	
	<string name="how_change_pin_title">
	    How do I change my PIN?
	</string>
	<string name="how_change_pin_body">
	    To change your PIN, please call 1-800-983-1266; 
	    you will be prompted to enter your current PIN and then your new desired PIN.
	</string>
	
	<string name="daily_withdrawal_limit_title">
		Is there a daily ATM withdrawal limit?
	</string>
	<string name="daily_withdrawal_limit_body">
	    Yes. The maximum amount you can withdraw from ATMs is $510.00 per day.
	    The Discover ATM withdrawal limit is $510 per day. 
	    Some ATMs may have lower withdrawal limits but you can complete multiple transactions 
	    until you meet the Discover withdrawal limit of $510 per day.
	</string>
	
	<string name="atm_withdrawal_fees_title">
		Is there a fee for using my debit card at an ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="atm_withdrawal_fees_body">
	    60,000 Allpoint&#174; and MoneyPass&#174; ATMs are completely free of charge. 
	    However, owners of a non-MoneyPass/Allpoint ATM may charge a fee.
	    
	    Discover will not charge you a fee for using your debit card at any ATM.
	</string>
	
	<string name="surcharge_free_title">
	    How do I find a surcharge-free ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="surcharge_free_body">
	    To display only surcharge-free ATMs on your search, enable the "Display only Surcharge-Free ATMs" toggle. Surcharge-free ATMs are represented by orange icons in map and list view.
	</string>
	
	<string name="outside_us_use_title">
	    Can I use my debit card outside of the United States? 
	</string>
	<string name="outside_us_use_body">
	    Your Discover debit card is accepted at participating merchants in the United States, 
	    Canada, Mexico and the Caribbean wherever you see a Discover, PULSE&#174; or Diners Club International&#174; logo.
	</string>
	
	<string name="deposit_to_atm_title">
	    Can I make a deposit at an ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="deposit_to_atm_body">
		Currently, Discover Bank does not accept deposits at ATM locations (other than at its branch in Greenwood, DE).
		 If you need to deposit a check, please use the mobile check deposit 
		 feature on Discover’s mobile app or mail it to us at:
		 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discover Bank
		 &lt;br&gt;P.O. Box 30417
		 &lt;br&gt;Salt Lake City, UT 84130
	</string>
	
	<string name="wrongfully_charged_title">
	    What happens if I am charged an ATM fee at an Allpoint&#174; MoneyPass location?
	</string>
	<string name="wrongfully_charged_body">
	    If you are at an Allpoint® or MoneyPass® ATM and it indicates you are being charged a fee, 
	    accept the fee and proceed with your transactions. Then notify Discover Bank by sending a message 
	    through our Secure Message Center or by calling us at 1-800-347-7000.  
	   	&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
	    Please provide the following information and we will credit your account for a fee:
		&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
		&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;•&#160; Date and time of the transaction&lt;br&gt;
		&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;•&#160; ATM location&lt;br&gt;
		&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;•&#160; Last four digits of your debit card&lt;br&gt;
		&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;•&#160; Amount of the fee you were charged
	</string><!-- Using &#160; to enforce indent as text is read-in as HTML (\t will not work) -->
	
	<string name="surcharge_free_fees_title">
		Are there any fees associated with the use of a surcharge-free ATM?
	</string>
	<string name="surcharge_free_fees_body">
		You will not be charged an ATM surcharge when you withdraw cash with your Discover debit card 
		at the surcharge-free ATMs represented by orange map pins. 
		If you take a cash advance with your Discover credit card at one of these locations, 
		you will not be charged an ATM surcharge fee but your cash advance APR and cash advance fee will apply. 
		ATM surcharge fees may apply to Discover cash withdrawals at other ATMs not designated “Surcharge-Free.”
	</string>
	
</resources>



