<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string-array name="card_extra_faq_array">
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_one</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_one</item>
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_two</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_two</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_three</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_three</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_four</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_four</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_five</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_five</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_six</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_six</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_seven</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_seven</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_eight</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_eight</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_nine</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_nine</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_extra_title_ten</item>
        <item>@string/card_extra_content_ten</item>  
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_one">What is Discover Extras?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_one">
        Discover Extras is another way you can save money on purchases at your favorite merchants. 
        When you take advantage of an Extras offer, many of these will result in a statement credit on your 
        Discover account while some offers may be instant savings. If you are offered instant savings, 
        you will simply show the offer when making your purchase to receive your savings.  
        Please be sure to read your offer details to see how to get your savings.
    </string>
     
    <string name="card_extra_title_two">How do I receive Discover Extras?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_two">
        If you are already receiving marketing emails from us, you will be eligible to receive the offers. 
        If you don’t have a valid email address on file or have opted out of marketing emails, 
        you will need to update your settings via your Account Profile on Discover.com. Once you are logged in, 
        click on “Account Profile” at the top of the page and scroll down until you see the option for “Offers” 
        and click to sign up for “Offers by E-mail/Text.”  If you do not have a valid email address on file, 
        you will need to edit your contact information on this same page.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_three">How do Discover Extras work?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_three">
        Many Discover Extras are offers that may result in statement credits for purchases you make at merchants you frequently shop at.  
        If you have an offer you’d like to take advantage of, please check the offer details to see how your savings will work. 
        If your offer is a statement credit, use your Discover Card within the specified dates and your account will be credited within 14 days. 
        If your offer is a coupon, show the coupon when making your purchase to get your savings.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_four">How do I know if I have received a Discover Extra?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_four">
        You will receive an email to the email address we have on file. The expiration date is shown on the offer.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_five">Do Discover Extras expire?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_five">
        Yes. All offers will eventually expire.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_six">What will the statement credit look like on my statement?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_six">
        On your statement it will say: Discover Extra at (merchant).
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_seven">Am I charged a fee if I receive a Discover Extra?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_seven">
        No. There are no additional or hidden fees associated with receiving or using a Discover Extra.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_eight">What do the different colored indicators signify?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_eight">
        The Red indicator means that you have three days or less to redeem your Extra offer. 
        Yellow represents four to 10 days before your order will expire. 
        Green shows that you have more than 10 days before your Extra offer will expire. 
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_nine">What merchant locations does the map show?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_nine">
       The map will show merchant locations within your 15 mile radius or a 15 mile radius of the city or zip you are searching.  
       If there are no merchant locations in your search area, your map will not show any results.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_extra_title_ten">What do I do if I have questions about my offers?</string>
    <string name="card_extra_content_ten">
        Please call us at 1-800-DISCOVER (1-800-347-2683).
    </string>
    
    
    
</resources>