<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="E_401">Sorry. The User ID and/or Password does not match our records, or you are not registered. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="E_503">Some of our web site features are unavailable at this time. We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_4031110">We are working on making enhancements to our mobile app. During this time, the mobile app will not be available for Discover Business Card, Essential Card and Corporate Card accounts. We expect it to be up and running by July 22, 2013. Please sign in through our mobile site at m.discover.com to access your account information. Thank you.</string>
    <string name="E_4011103">You have one more log in attempt today. For security purposes, we limit the number of attempts to enter your information. If you think you are receiving this message in error, call 1-877-742-7822</string>
    <string name="E_4011107">Your temporary password has been used or is expired.</string>
    <string name="E_4031101">We know you’re excited to get into the app, but you’ve tried to log in with the wrong username or password too many times. Please contact Customer Service at 1-877-742-7822 for assistance</string>
    <string name="E_4031104">Your online access is still being set up. Please try back again	later.</string>
    <string name="E_4031105">We\'re sorry, you may no longer use this Discover card account number to access the app. Instead, please visit www.discover.com to create User ID and password. If you have any questions, please contact Customer Service at 1-877-742-7822</string>
    <string name="E_4031105_WITHUSERID">We\'re Sorry, you may no longer use this Discover Card account number	to access the app. Instead, please log in using	your User ID and Password. !~~! "&lt;br&#47;&gt;""&lt;br&#47;&gt; If you have any questions, please contact Customer Service at 1-877-742-7822</string>
    <string name="E_4031106">Your Discover Card Account Number has been changed. In order to	access your account through the mobile channel, you must first log in to the Account Center on www.discover.com. For more information, please contact Customer Service at 1-877-742-7822</string>
    <string name="E_4031401_NOTENROLLED">Help us keep your account safe by visiting discover.com on your primary computer to establish your set of security questions.</string>
    <string name="E_4031402">For security purposes, your online account has been locked.Please call Discover Customer Service at	1-888-251-8003 for information about accessing your account online.</string>
    <string name="E_4031402_LOCKOUT">For security purposes, your online account has been locked."&lt;br&#47;&gt;""&lt;br&#47;&gt;Please call Discover Customer Service at 1-888-251-8003 for information about accessing your account online.</string>
    <string name="E_4031401_DENY">LOST CARD.</string>
    <string name="E_4031401_UNLOCKED">Help us keep your account safe by visiting discover.com on your primary PC to establish your set of security questions.</string>
    <string name="E_4031401_UNVERIFIED">Help us keep your account safe by visiting discover.com on your primary PC to establish your set of security questions.</string>
    <string name="E_4031401_LOCKOUT">For security purposes, your online account has been locked.Please call Discover Customer Service at 1-888-251-8003 for information about accessing your account online.</string>
    <string name="E_0">We\'re sorry.Some of our web site features are unavailable at this time. We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_4031102">Due to special conditions related to your account, we could not complete your request. Please contact Customer Service at 1-800-347-2683.</string>
    <string name="E_4031102_SSO_DELINK">Due to special conditions related to your credit card account, we can\'t provide you with access to your account information at this time."&lt;br&#47;&gt;""&lt;br&#47;&gt;To recover your User ID, you will need to re-register for online account access at DiscoverBank.com.</string>
    <string name="E_4031102_SSO_DELINK_BUTTON">true.</string>
    <!-- Defect ID: 95998 -->
    <string name="E_4031102_SSO">We are unable to load your Discover Bank Account(s). Please contact Customer Service at 1-800-347-2683 so we can verify your social security number.</string>
    <!-- Defect ID: 95998 -->
    <string name="E_4031102_SSN_NOT_MATCH">We are unable to load your Discover Bank Account(s). Please contact Customer Service at 1-800-347-2683 so we can verify your social security number.</string>
    <string name="E_4031102_SSO_AccountNo">Can not Login with Account Number.</string>
    <string name="E_40311021">SSN NOT MATCHED !!</string>
    <string name="E_4031102_SSO_BUTTON">true.</string>
    <string name="E_1601">Promotion code is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1602">Please enter a valid promotion code.</string>
    <string name="E_1603">This Promotion is already enrolled.</string>
    <string name="E_1604">Failed to enroll the promotion.</string>
    <string name="E_1625">We are sorry. You are ineligible to access this rewards service.</string>
    <string name="E_500">Discover.com Mobile Error We\'re sorry. Your request cannot be completed at this time. We sincerely apologize for this inconvenience and are working to resolve this issue soon. For further assistance please call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_415">Unsupported Media Type.</string>
    <string name="E_1624">We are sorry. You are ineligible for redemption.</string>
    <string name="E_1628">Cashback Bonus is currently unavailable. We apologize for the inconvenience. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="E_1629">Account is in Bad status.</string>
    <string name="E_1601">Promotion Code is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1602">Please Enter valid Promotion Code.</string>
    <string name="E_1603">This promotion is already enrolled.</string>
    <string name="E_1604">Fail to enroll the promotion.</string>
    <string name="E_1605">Mode code is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1606">Please enter a valid mode code.</string>
    <string name="E_1608">You do not have sufficient cash back balance to redeem.</string>
    <string name="E_1609">You must have a bank account on file in order to redeem Direct	Deposit.</string>
    <string name="E_1610">Amount is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1611">Please enter an amount using only number and a decimal point. Do not dollar signs and commas(e.g. 1000.00).</string>
    <string name="E_1612">No Disbursement Units available.</string>
    <string name="E_1613">Emergency mode closure.</string>
    <string name="E_1614">Please enter a valid hashed Account number.</string>
    <string name="E_1615">Please enter a valid hashed Routing number.</string>
    <string name="E_1616">No Bank Account fount for the given Account Number and Routing	Number combination.</string>
    <string name="E_1617">E-Certificate Number is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1618">Order-Id is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1619">Order-Date is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1620">Please enter a valid orderdate in MM/DD/YYYY format.</string>
    <string name="E_1621">Failed to add order item in the cart.</string>
    <string name="E_1622">Failed to submit the order.</string>
    <string name="E_1623">Failed to submit the order.May not have enough balance to submit the order.</string>
    <string name="E_1624">We are Sorry. You are ineligible for redeemption.</string>
    <string name="E_1625">We are sorry. You are ineligible to access this rewards service.</string>
    <string name="E_1626">Device Type is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1627">Please enter valid Device Type.</string>
    <string name="E_1628">Cashback Bonus is currently unavailable. We apologize for the inconvenience. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="E_1629">Account is in Bad staus.</string>
    <string name="E_1630">Order quantity is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1631">Please enter a valid integer value for order quantity greater than 0.</string>
    <string name="E_1632">Order quantity must not be greater than 1.</string>
    <string name="E_1633">No data found.</string>
    <string name="E_1634">Redemption amount must be in increments of minDisbAmt.</string>
    <string name="E_1635">Please enter a valid Parterns value.</string>
    <string name="E_1636">We are Sorry. This E-Certificate is not available to redeem now.</string>
    <string name="E_1642">We are sorry. You are ineligible to access this rewards service.</string>
    <string name="E_1701">Send MoneyYour account is not eligible to use this service at this time. If you have questions about your eligibility, please call	us at 1-800-DISCOVER.</string>
    <string name="E_1702">Some of our web site features are unavailable at this time. We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_1703">Email not registered.</string>
    <string name="E_1704">We\'re Sorry. You\'ve reached your Discover Money Messenger monthly limit of $ $$Monthlylimit$$. You can send money again starting next month.</string>
    <string name="E_1705">We\'re sorry.You\'ve reached your discover money messenger daily limit of $ $$Dailylimit$$. You can send money again starting tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="E_1706">Service unavailable.We\'re sorry, We are experiencing temporary	technical difficulties. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="E_1707">Your Email Address is Required.</string>
    <string name="E_1708">E-mail Address entered is not valid. Please enter it again.</string>
    <string name="E_1709">Recipient’s name is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1710">Recipient\'s Name cannot contain the special characters you	entered.</string>
    <string name="E_1711">Recipient\'s Name doesn\'t meet our acceptable use guidelines.Please remove or use a different name.</string>
    <string name="E_1712">Recipient\'s E-mail or Mobile Phone Number is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1713">E-mail Address entered is not valid. Please enter it again.</string>
    <string name="E_1714">A valid phone number format is 000-000-0000.</string>
    <string name="E_1715">You cannot send money to yourself. Please enter the Recipient\'s E-mail or Mobile Phone Number.</string>
    <string name="E_1716">Recipient\'s Mobile Phone Number cannot start with 0. (or) Recipient\'s Mobile Phone Number cannot start with 1.</string>
    <string name="E_1717">Amount is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1718">Amount can only contain numbers and a decimal point.</string>
    <string name="E_1719">Transaction Type is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1720">Please enter valid Transaction Type. TransactionType should be	(Friends or Family/ Pay for Goods).</string>
    <string name="E_1721">Please enter positive integer value for size.</string>
    <string name="E_1722">Please enter positive integer value for startIndex.</string>
    <string name="E_1723">Status Type is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1724">Status Type is invalid.</string>
    <string name="E_1725">Transaction id is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1726">Invalid transaction id.</string>
    <string name="E_1727">Request Type is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1728">This transaction cannot be cancelled. This payment was already	claimed by the recipient. The status of the transaction will be	updated to reflect this.</string>
    <string name="E_1729">This transaction cannot be cancelled. This payment was already	claimed by the recipient . The status of the transaction will be updated to reflect this.</string>
    <string name="E_1730">Some of our web site features are unavailable at this time. We	sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_1730_confirmTransaction">Service Unavailable Some of our web site features are unavailable at this time. We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_1730_cancelTransaction">Some of our web site features are unavailable at	this time. We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience	and are working	to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_1731">Show Status is required.</string>
    <string name="E_1732">Invalid Boolean Value.</string>
    <string name="E_1733">Please enter the E-mail Address not more than 100 characters.</string>
    <string name="E_1734">Amount can contain only two numbers after the decimal point.</string>
    <string name="E_Blank_Name">Enter Name.</string>
    <string name="E_noTransactions">Transaction HistoryThere is no transaction history to view.</string>
    <string name="E_No_special_characters">Recipients Name cannot contain the special characters you	entered.</string>
    <string name="E_Exceed_Monthly_Limit">Amount entered will cause you to exceed your monthly limit.</string>
    <string name="E_Exceed_Daily_Limit">Amount entered will cause you to exceed your daily limit.</string>
    <string name="E_Amount_Required">Amount is required.</string>
    <string name="E_Decimal_Point">Amount can contain only two numbers after a decimal point.</string>
    <string name="E_Only_Numbers">Amount can contain only numbers and a decimal point.</string>
    <string name="E_Ten_Digit_Number">Recipient\'s Mobile Phone Number is invalid. please enter 10 numbers.</string>
    <string name="E_Number_cannot_start1">Recipient\'s Mobile number cannot start with 1.</string>
    <string name="E_Number_cannot_start0">Recipient\'s Mobile number cannot start with 0.</string>
    <string name="E_Email_phone_required">Recipient\'s E-mail or Mobile Phone Number is required.</string>
    <string name="E_No_Money_Yourself">You cannot send money to yourself. Please enter recipient\'s E-mail or Mobile phone Number.</string>
    <string name="E_Daily_Limit">We\'re Sorry.You\'ve reached your Daily Limit.</string>
    <string name="E_Monthly_Limit">We\'re Sorry.You\'ve reached your Monthly Limit.</string>
    <string name="E_Invalid_email">Recipient\'s E-mail address entered is not valid. Please enter it again.</string>
    <string name="E_Invalid_phone">Recipient\'s Mobile Number is invalid. Please enter 10 numbers.</string>
    <string name="E_INSUFFICIENT_CBB_BALANCE_FOR_REDEEM_ECERT">$$name$$ Redeem Cashback Bonus Cashback Bonus	$$redeemLanding_CashBackBonusBalance$$ $$ACHome_CashBackBonusBalance$$	$$pageError_errorMessage$$ We\'re sorry, but you do not have sufficient Cashback Bonus to issue an eCertificate at this time.</string>
    <string name="E_INSUFFICIENT_CBB_BALANCE_FOR_REDEEM_STATEMENT_CREDIT">We\'re sorry, but you do not have sufficient Bonus Statement Credit redemptions are available in increments of $$statement_credit_minDisbIncrAmt$$.</string>
    <string name="E_INSUFFICIENT_CBB_BALANCE_FOR_REDEEM_DIRECT_DEPOSIT">We\'re sorry, but you do not have sufficient Cashback Bonus to issue a Direct Deposit at this time. Direct Depost redemptions are available in increments of $$directDeposit1_minDisbIncrAmt$$.</string>
    <string name="E_403">For security purposes, your online account has been	locked.Please call Discover Customer Service at	1-888-251-8003 for information about accessing your account online.</string>
    <string name="E_acLiteOutageMode">Some of our website features are unavailable at this	time. We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_acLiteOutageMode_ACL">We\'re sorry.Some of our website features are unavailable at this time. We sincerely apologize	for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue soon.</string>
    <string name="E_1403">We\'re sorry. We are experiencing technical difficulties with the service you are trying to access.</string>
    <string name="E_1404">We are currently experiencing technical difficulties. We apologize for the inconvenience.Please try again later or contact Customer Service at 1-800-DISCOVER (1-800-347-2683).</string>
    <string name="E_1401_LOCKOUT">Secure Credit Card LoginFor security purposes, your online account has been locked. Please call Discover Customer Service at 1-888-251-8003 for information about accessing your account online.</string>
    <string name="E_1401_CREATEUSER">SA ERROR CREATE USER.</string>
    <string name="E_skipped"> We\'re sorry.Some of our web site features are unavailable at this time. We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_1402_LOCKOUT">For security purposes, your online account has been	locked.Please call Discover Customer Service at	1-888-251-8003 for information about accessing your account online.</string>
    <string name="E_1005">We\'re sorry.Some of our web site features are unavailable at	this time. We sincerely apologize for this temporary inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_1201">Make a Payment: To make a Secure Online Payment you must first add an external bank account.</string>
    <string name="E_1204">Make a Payment:There are no dates left for you to make a payment. For	assistance, please call 1-877-742-7822</string>
    <string name="E_1207">Payment amount must be between $0.01 and $99,999.99.</string>
    <string name="E_1208">Your payment cannot be more than your current balance of $$currentBalance$$.</string>
    <string name="E_1209">You have already scheduled a payment for this statement. Your	maximum payment amount cannot be greater than your current outstanding balance of $$outstandingBalance$$.</string>
    <string name="E_1210">Please enter an amount using only numerals and a decimal point. Do not use dollar signs and commas (e.g. 1000.00).</string>
    <string name="E_1213">Please enter a valid payment date in MM/dd/yyyy format.</string>
    <string name="E_1214">Please enter a valid payment open date in MM/dd/yyyy format.</string>
    <string name="E_1215">Make a Payment We\'re sorry. We are unable to process your	request	at this time. There is a problem with your bank account on file. Please contact customer service at 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_1216">You are unable to make a payment at this time. No payment is due at this time. You have a zero or credit balance. For assistance,	please call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_1216_Confirm_Payment">Make a PaymentYou are unable to make a payment at this time. No payment is due at this time. You have a zero or credit balance. For assistance, please call</string>
    <string name="E_1217">You are unable to make a payment at this time.Your pending payments total is $$pendingPayments$$ and your current balance is $$currentBalance$$. Making additional payments to your Account will	result in a credit balance. If you would like to view these payments select \"Pending Payments\". To cancel or edit payments, please visit	the Account Center at www.discover.com.</string>
    <string name="E_1217_Confirm_Payment">Make a PaymentYou are unable to make a payment at this time.Your pending payments total is $$pendingPayments$$ and your current balance is $!~currentBalance~!. Making additional payments to your Account will result in a credit balance. If you would like to view these payments select \"Pending Payments\". To cancel or edit payments, please visit the Account Center at www.discover.com.</string>
    <string name="E_1218">Some of our website features are unavailable at this time	resulting in limited access to functionality. We cannot accept your	additional payment request at this time, however, we are able to process the previous payment you made which is listed below for your reference.</string>
    <string name="E_Make_Payment_1218">Make a Payment:!~errormessage~!</string>
    <string name="E_1219">Make a Payment:Some of our website features are unavailable at this time. We can, however, process payments for the current day only.	For a future date, please try again later. We thank you for your patience.</string>
    <string name="E_1220">Bank short name required.</string>
    <string name="E_1221">Provide valid bank short name.</string>
    <string name="E_1222">Payment amount required.</string>
    <string name="E_1223">Payment date required.</string>
    <string name="E_1224">HA Mode Required.</string>
    <string name="E_1225">Provide valid HA mode (either true or false).</string>
    <string name="E_1226">We\'re unable to process your payment at this time because the	following payment was submitted to your account while you were	making a payment, from the same account.</string>
    <string name="E_1227">We\'re unable to process your payment at this time because the	following payment was submitted to your account while you were making a payment, and the maximum number of payments per day has been reached.</string>
    <string name="E_1228PB">Make a Payment:We\'re unable to process your online payment today because it is past the cutt-off time and you have no available	payment dates. For assistance call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_1229PB">Make a Payment:We\'re unable to process your online payment today because it is past the cutt-off time and you have no available payment dates for the selected bank account. You can make a payment	by selecting a different bank account. For assistance call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_1230PB">Make a Payment: class=\'redtext\'You have missed the cut-off time that would allow your payment to be credited to your account as of today.Your next available payment posting date is !~nextAvailableDate~!.	If you would like to submit your payment of $!~payAmount~! using this date please Submit below.</string>
    <string name="E_1228">Make a Payment:We are unable to process your online payment today	because it is past the 5:00pm Eastern Time cut off and you have	no available payment dates. For assistance call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_1229">Make a Payment:We’re unable to process your online payment because	it is past the 5:00pm Eastern Time cutoff time and you have no available payment dates for the selected bank account. You can make a payment by selecting a different bank account. For assistance call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_1230">Make a Payment: You have missed the Eastern Time cut off for submitting a payment that will post today. Your next	available payment posting date is !~nextAvailableDate~!. If you would like to submit your payment of $!~payAmount~! using this date please Submitbelow.</string>
    <string name="E_1231">Your bank account is problematic, provide valid bank short name.
</string>
    <string name="E_1232">Make a PaymentSome of our website features are unavailable at this time resulting in limited access to functionality and can process payments for the current day only. If you would like to schedule a payment for a future date, please try again later. We	thank you for your patience.</string>
    <string name="E_1233">Make a PaymentSome of our website features are unavailable at this	time resulting in limited access to functionality.We can however,process payments for the current day only. If you would like to schedule a payment for a future date,please try again later. We thank you for your patience.</string>
    <string name="E_1234">Hashed account number required. Please enter a valid hashed account number.</string>
    <string name="E_1235">Hashed routing number required. Please enter a valid hashed routing number.</string>
    <string name="E_1236">Provide valid bank information.</string>
    <string name="E_Update_HighLighted">Your request cannot be processed. Please update the highlighted area(s) below.</string>
    <string name="E_NoDates_for_Bank">There are no available payment dates for your selected bank account. Please select a different bank account to continue.</string>
    <string name="E_Last_Stmt_Range"> In order to make a payment your Last Statement	balance must be	between $0.01 and $99,999.99 .</string>
    <string name="E_Curr_Baln_Range"> In order to make a payment your Current balance must be between $0.01 and $99,999.99 .</string>
    <string name="E_Pay_func_unavail">Some of our website features are unavailable at this time resulting in limited access to functionality and can process	payments for the current day only. If you would like to schedule a payment for a future date, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="E_Days_Delinquent">Your account is past due. Please pay your minimum monthly payment plus the past due amount.</string>
    <string name="E_Over_Limit">You are $ $$overLimitAmount$$ over your Account\'s credit line.</string>
    <string name="E_PARM_PAY_ZERO">You are unable to make a payment at this time. No payment is due at this time. You have a zero or credit balance. For assistance,	please call 1-877-742-7822	</string>
    <string name="E_NO_MIN_PAY">You have no payment due at this time.</string>
    <string name="E_Is_cutoffPB"> Your payment will be credited to your account as of the date selected.</string>
    <string name="E_Is_cutoff"> Payments made after 5p.m. Eastern Time will post on the next	day.</string>
    <string name="E_safeSecure">For the safety and security of your account, if you make	payments more often than every 3 days, your payments may not be	reflected in your available credit for up to 8 days.</string>
    <string name="E_BAD_DATE">We cannot process 2 payments from the same bank account on the same day.If you would like to make a payment on the date you selected you\'ll need to choose a different account or cancel your	previously scheduled payment.</string>
    <string name="E_BAD_BANK">Account selected, $$bankAccount$$ is invalid. Choose another account or resolve with your bank.</string>
    <string name="E_Select_Bank">Your request cannot be processed. Please select a bank account.</string>
    <string name="E_Conflict_Payment">Make a Payment: !~errormessage~!</string>
    <string name="E_5031006">We\'re sorry. We will be performing a system maintenance between	1 a.m. and 6 a.m. Eastern Time. We apologize for any inconvenience.	Please try again later.	</string>
    <string name="E_5031007">We\'re sorry. We are currently updating our system and cannot complete your request at this time. We apologize for any inconvenience. Please	try again later. </string>
    <string name="E_5031008">We\'re sorry. We will be performing a system maintenance between	1 a.m. and 6 a.m. Eastern Time. We apologize for any inconvenience.	Please try again later, or for immediate assistance call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_5031108">We apologize for the temporary inconvenience.Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="E_OPTIONAL_UPGRADE">An updated version of application is now available! Please update	to the newest version to take advantage of all the latest features and performance and security enhancements.</string>
    <string name="E_pendingPayErrMsg">Some of our website features are unavailable at this time resulting in limited access to functionality. Your most recent pending payment is listed below. Please note that we can only	display	this one pending payment, even if you have others scheduled.</string>
    <string name="E_payConfirmBack">Make a Payment: There may have been a problem with your payment request. To verify that the payment was submitted please	check your Pending Payments \ For assistance please call 1-877-742-7822</string>
    <string name="E_REDEEM_BAD_ACCOUNT_STATUS"> $$name$$ Redeem Cashback BonusCashback $$redeemLanding_CashBackBonusBalance$$ $$ACHome_CashBackBonusBalance$$ $$pageError_errorMessage$$ We\'re sorry, but your current account status will not allow a redemption. lf you have questions, please contact Customer Service at	1-800-DISCOVER.</string>
    <string name="E_REDEEM_EMC_STATUS"> $$name$$ Redeem Cashback BonusCashback $$redeemLanding_CashBackBonusBalance$$ $$ACHome_CashBackBonusBalance$$ $$pageError_errorMessage$$ There is either a problem with the Partner you have selected or it is no longer available.</string>
    <string name="E_INELIGIBLE_DISCOVER_GIFTCARDS"> $$name$$ Discover Gift Cards	$$pageError_errorMessage$$ We\'re Sorry.Due to regulations in your state, you are not eligible to redeem for the Discover Gift Card.Please call 1-800-DISCOVER (1-800-347-2683) if you have further questions.</string>
    <string name="E_REFER_A_FRIEND_ACCT_INELIGIBLE">Your account is not eligible to make referrals at this time. We apologize for the inconvenience.</string>
    <string name="E_SecurityTestFail">Enhanced Account Security.We\'re sorry. Our services are unavailable at this time. We apologize for any inconvenience.</string>
    <string name="E_2002">No record found.</string>
    <string name="E_2011">You are not eligible for Extras.</string>
    <string name="E_2003">ZipCode is required.</string>
    <string name="E_2004">Please enter a valid zipCode.</string>
    <string name="E_2001">CampaignId is required.</string>
    <string name="E_2005">Latitude is required.</string>
    <string name="E_2006">Longitude is required.</string>
    <string name="E_2007">$$name$$ Thanks for visiting $$pageError_errorMessage$$ At this time we don\'t have any Extras available. Be sure to check back soon,to find new offers you can take advantage of. Redeem your	Bonus for eCertificates, Partner gift cards and more.</string>
    <string name="E_2007_MI"> $$name$$ Thanks for visiting $$pageError_errorMessage$$ At this time we don\'t have any Extras available. Be sure to check back soon, to find new offers you can take advantage of.</string>
    <string name="E_2008">Please enter a valid latitude.</string>
    <string name="E_2009">Please enter a valid longitude."</string>
    <!-- <string name="E_5031108">Secure Credit Card Log In.</string> -->
    <string name="E_4031401_LOCKOUT">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_4031402">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <!-- <string name="E_4031401_NOTENROLLED">Enhanced Account Security</string> -->
    <!-- <string name="E_4031401_UNVERIFIED">Enhanced Account Security</string> -->
    <!-- <string name="E_4031401_UNLOCKED">Enhanced Account Security</string> -->


    <!-- Error message for push notification -->
    <string name="E_Push_Other_Account">Changes have been made to push alerts. Update your settings to continue receiving alerts</string>

    <!-- NEW CODES Titles -->

    <string name="E_T_5031108">Cashback Bonus is Currently Unavailable</string>
    <string name="E_T_1401_LOCKOUT">Secure Credit Card Login</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031102_SSO_DELINK">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031102_SSO">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031401_DENY">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031106">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031101"> You\'ve Been Locked Out</string>
    <string name="E_T_503">Oops!</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031110">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_100">Network Connection Error</string>
    <string name="E_100">The network connection appears to be offline at this moment. Please check your device settings and try again once the connection has been restored.</string>
    <string name="E_T_403">You\'ve Been Locked Out</string>
    <string name="E_T_0">Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_1401"> Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_T_1402"> You\'ve Been Locked Out</string>
    <string name="E_T_1910"></string>
    <string name="E_T_1905"> We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_1910"></string>
    <string name="E_T_1102"></string>
    <string name="E_T_1911"> Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_1102"> Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_1906"></string>
    <string name="E_T_1912"> Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_1913"> Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_1907"> Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_1008"> Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031104"> We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031105_WITHUSERID">Card Number Error</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031102"> We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031105">Card Number Error</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031402">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031402_LOCKOUT">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031401_UNLOCKED">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031401_NOTENROLLED">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031401_UNVERIFIED">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031401_LOCKOUT">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_T_1402_LOCKOUT">Enhanced Account Security</string>
    <string name="E_T_5031006">Performing System Maintenance</string>
    <string name="E_T_5031007">Performing System Maintenance</string>
    <!-- <string name="E_T_503">Performing System Maintenance</string> -->
    <string name="E_T_4011107">Password Error</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031102_SSN_NOT_MATCH">We\'re Sorry</string>

    <!-- New Codes Message -->
    <string name="E_1401">Help us keep your account safe by visiting discover.com on your primary computer to establish your set of security questions.</string>
    <string name="E_1402">We know you’re excited to get into the app, but you’ve tried to log in with the wrong username or password too many times. Please contact us at 1-877-742-7822 or use our enhanced account security to regain access to your account.</string>
    <string name="E_1910">We know you’re excited to get into the app, but you’ve tried to log in with the wrong username or password too many times. Please contact us at 1-877-742-7822 or use our enhanced account security to regain access to your account.</string>
    <string name="E_1905">As a Sam\'s Club Discover Cardmember, you cannot register for Account Center access at discover.com. We\'d love to have you, but for now you must register through the Sam\'s Club Website to manage your account.</string>
    <string name="E_1910">You have one more login attempt today.  For security purposes, we limit the number of attempts to enter your information. If you think you are receiving this message in error, call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_1906">You have entered invalid information.Carefully review your information and please try again.</string>
    <string name="E_1102">Due to special conditions related to your account, we cannot provide you with access to discover.com Mobile at this time.  Please contact customer service at 1-877-742-7822 for more information or assistance.</string>
    <string name="E_1911">Due to special conditions related to your account, we cannot provide you with access to discover.com Mobile at this time. 
	     Please contact customer service at 1-877-742-7822 for more information or assistance.</string>
    <string name="E_1912">Due to special conditions related to your account, we cannot provide you with access to discover.com Mobile at this time. 
	     Please contact customer service at 1-877-742-7822 for more information or assistance.</string>
    <string name="E_1913">Due to special conditions related to your account, we cannot provide you with access to discover.com Mobile at this time. 
	     Please contact customer service at 1-877-742-7822 for more information or assistance.</string>
    <string name="E_1907">Due to special conditions related to your account, we cannot provide you with access to discover.com Mobile at this time. 
	     Please contact customer service at 1-877-742-7822 for more information or assistance.</string>
    <string name="E_1008">We will be performing a system maintenance between 1 a.m. and 6 a.m. Eastern Time. We apologize for any inconvenience. Please try again later, or for immediate assistance call 18777427822</string>
    <string name="E_1916">You have entered invalid information.Carefully review your information and please try again.</string>

    <!-- Registration Code title -->
    <!-- DEFECT ID:97030 -->
    <string name="E_T_4031928">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <!-- DEFECT ID:97030 -->
    <string name="E_T_4001905">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_5001905">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_5031905">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031905">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4001907">Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_5001908">Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_4001910">You\'ve Been Locked Out</string>
    <string name="E_T_4001911">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4001912">Your Request Could Not Be Completed</string>
    <string name="E_T_4001913">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <!-- DEFECT ID:96742 -->
    <string name="E_T_4001914">Please Contact Customer Service</string>
    <!-- DEFECT ID:96742 -->
    <string name="E_T_4001915">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4001916">We\'re Sorry</string>
    <string name="E_T_4031922">Secure Credit Card Log In</string>

    <!-- Registration code Messages -->
    <string name="E_4001901">Invalid user input</string>
    <string name="E_4001902">User IDs do not match.</string>
    <string name="E_4001903">Passwords do not match.</string>
    <string name="E_4001904">Email is required and must be a valid address.</string>
    <string name="E_4001905">As a Sam\'s Club Discover Cardmember, you cannot register for Account Center access at discover.com. We\'d love to have you, but for now you must register through the Sam\'s Club Website to manage your account.</string>
    <string name="E_5001905">As a Sam\'s Club Discover Cardmember, you cannot register for Account Center access at discover.com. We\'d love to have you, but for now you must register through the Sam\'s Club Website to manage your account.</string>
    <string name="E_5031905">As a Sam\'s Club Discover Cardmember, you cannot register for Account Center access at discover.com. We\'d love to have you, but for now you must register through the Sam\'s Club Website to manage your account.</string>
    <string name="E_4031905">As a Sam\'s Club Discover Cardmember, you cannot register for Account Center access at discover.com. We\'d love to have you, but for now you must register through the Sam\'s Club Website to manage your account.</string>
    <string name="E_5001906">You have entered invalid information.  Carefully review your information and please try again.</string>
    <string name="E_5031906">You have entered invalid information.  Carefully review your information and please try again.</string>
    <string name="E_4001907">There was a problem authenticating your registration information.</string>
    <string name="E_5001908">The information you entered was not valid.If you feel that you have received this message in error return to the Forgot Your Password page , and enter your information again.</string>
    <string name="E_5001909">Problem retrieving account information</string>
    <string name="E_4001910">We know you\'re excited to get into the app, but you\'ve tried to log in with the wrong username or password too many times."&lt;br&#47;&gt;""&lt;br&#47;&gt;Please contact Customer Service at 1-877-742-7822 for assistance.</string>
    <string name="E_4001911">Due to special conditions related to your account, we could not complete your request. Please contact Customer Service at 1-800-347-2683.</string>
    <string name="E_4001912">Due to special conditions related to your account, we cannot provide you with access to discover.com Mobile at this time. 
	     Please contact customer service at 1-877-742-7822 for more information or assistance.</string>
    <string name="E_4001913">Due to special conditions related to your account, we could not complete your request. Please contact Customer Service at 1-800-347-2683.</string>
    <!-- DEFECT ID:96742 -->
    <string name="E_4001914">We\'re sorry, but the primary Cardholder is the only one allowed to register for, and access the Account Center.</string>
    <!-- DEFECT ID:96742 -->
    <string name="E_4001915">Your request cannot be completed because the rewards application is currently under maintenance.We apologize for the inconvenience. Please try again later or contact Customer Service at 1-800-347-2683.</string>
    <string name="E_4001916">You have entered invalid information.Carefully review your information and please try again.</string>
    <string name="E_4001917">You have one more log in attempt today. For security purposes, we limit the number of attempts to enter your information. If you think you are receiving this message in error, call 1-877-742-7822.</string>
    <string name="E_4001918">Your Request Could Not Be Completed. The information entered was not valid. If you feel that you have received this message in error, return to the Forgot User ID/Password page and try again.</string>
    <string name="E_4001919">User ID and password must not be the same.</string>
    <string name="E_4001920">User ID must not look like your Social Security number. Please choose another one.</string>
    <string name="E_4001921">User ID is already in use. Please choose another one.</string>
    <string name="E_4031922">Your Discover Card Account Number has been changed. In order to	access your account through the mobile channel, you must first log in to the Account Center on www.discover.com. For more information, please contact Customer Service at 1-877-742-7822</string>
    <string name="E_4001923">The User ID is empty. Please enter a User ID.</string>
    <string name="E_4001924">The User ID is invalid. Please enter a valid User ID.</string>
    <string name="E_4001925">The password is empty. Please enter a password.</string>
    <string name="E_4001926">The password is invalid. Please enter a valid password.</string>
    <!-- DEFECT ID:97030 -->
    <string name="E_4031928">Due to special conditions related to your account, we can\'t retrieve your User ID at this time."&lt;br&#47;&gt;""&lt;br&#47;&gt;To recover your User ID, you will need to re-register for online account access.</string>
    <!-- DEFECT ID:97030 -->
    <string name="E_4031109"> Due to increased security requirements, you must create a new User ID to access your accounts. Please update your User ID at Discover.com.</string>

    <!-- need help footer and feedback -->
    <!-- 0 for hide need help footer and show feedback -->
    <!-- 1 for hide feedback link and show need help footer -->
    <!-- 2 for hide both -->
    <!-- 3 for show both -->
    <!-- 4 for show both feedback link and  need help footer and ok button navigate to logout activity -->
    <string name="E_H_4001910">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031101">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031402">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031401_LOCKOUT">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_403">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031402_LOCKOUT">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031102">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4001911">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4001913">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031102_SSO_DELINK">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031102_SSO">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031105">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031105_WITHUSERID">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031106">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_4011107">3</string>
    <string name="E_H_503">4</string>
    <string name="E_H_5031006">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_5031007">0</string>
    <string name="E_H_5031108">4</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031104">3</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031401_NOTENROLLED">3</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031401_UNLOCKED">3</string>
    <string name="E_H_4031401_UNVERIFIED">3</string>
    <string name="E_T_101">Timeout!</string>
    <string name="E_101">Getting slow network!</string>
    <string name="E_T_102">No Connection!</string>
    <string name="E_102">Could not connect to the server!</string>
    <string name="E_T_103">Malformed URL</string>
    <string name="E_103">Bad Request!</string>
    <string name="E_T_104">Connection Problem!</string>
    <string name="E_104">Could not connect to the server!</string>
    
    <string name="E_SA_SKIPPED_CONTENT">Some of our website features are unavailable at this time. We sincerely apologize for the inconvenience and are working to resolve the issue.</string>
    <string name="E_SA_SKIPPED_TITLE">We\'re Sorry</string>

</resources>