<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="privacyTerms">Privacy &amp; Terms</string>
    <string name="card_terms_privacy_statement">Mobile Privacy Statement</string>
    <string name="card_terms_of_use_heading">Mobile Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="card_privacy_title"><![CDATA[Discover Financial Services Mobile Privacy Statement]]></string>
    <string name="card_terms_of_use_title">Mobile Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="card_privacy_statement">
<![CDATA[<h3>This Mobile Privacy Statement applies to our mobile and social media apps and mobile websites.</h3>
    <p>This Mobile Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement") describes how Discover Financial Services (including Discover Bank, Discover Products Inc., and their affiliates) treat personal information on our mobile apps and websites, and apps on social media platforms ("Mobile Services").</p>
    <p>This Privacy Statement only describes Mobile Service practices.  It does not apply to how we generally collect or use your information as a customer of any Discover financial service or product.  It also doesn\'t apply to the practices on our websites not optimized for a mobile browser.</p>
    
    <h3>Our Mobile Services collect information from and about you.</h3>
    <p><strong>Information you submit</strong>.  For example, our Mobile Services may ask you to submit your name and account ID.  They may also ask for your email address or other contact information. We may collect your zip code to help you find an ATM.</p>
    <p><strong>Financial information</strong>.  For example, our Mobile Services may ask for bank account information for funds transfers to complete a service.  They may also ask for images of checks as part of a deposit.  How we use financial information is described in the privacy policies available on our
    <a href="https://www.discover.com/credit-cards/help-center/account/privacy-policies/index.html" target="_blank">website</a>.</p>
    <p><strong>Other information</strong>.  If you use our Mobile Services, we may collect information about the browser, device or operating system you\'re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. When you use our Mobile Services, we might collect your location using GPS, a cellular network location, wi-fi networks, browser services, or information you provide.</p>
    
    <h3>Our Mobile Services collect information in different ways.</h3>
    <p><strong>Information is collected directly from you</strong>. For example, we collect information if you request to receive offers and alerts through a Mobile Service.</p>
    <p><strong>Information is collected passively</strong>. Our Mobile Services may use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. Learn more about these tools, and how you can control them, here.</p>
    <p><strong>We get information about you from third parties</strong>. For example, our business partners and service providers may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information about you.</p>
    
    <h3>We use information from our Mobile Services in many ways.</h3>
    <p><strong>We use information to respond to your requests or questions</strong>. For example, we might use your information to complete a transaction that you requested.  We may also use your information to redeem your rewards or send you an alert you signed up for.</p>
    <p><strong>We use information to improve our products and services</strong>. We may use your information to make our Mobile Services better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.</p>
    <p><strong>We use information for security purposes</strong>. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.</p>
    
    <p><strong>We use information for marketing purposes.</strong>
    For example, we might send you information about new products and special offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. We may also use push notifications on our mobile apps. To manage this, read the choices section below.</p>
    <p><strong>We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.</strong>
    We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Privacy Statement or our Terms and Conditions.</p>
    <p><strong>We use information as otherwise permitted by law.</strong>
    We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Privacy Statement. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.</p>
    
    <h3>We may share information connected with our Mobile Services with third parties.</h3>
    
    <p><strong>We will share this information within the Discover Financial Services family of companies.</strong>
    For example, this includes Discover Bank and Discover Home Loans, Inc.  This also includes future Discover subsidiaries or affiliates. </p>
    
    <p><strong>We will share this information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.</strong>
    For example, we share information with vendors who send texts for us.  We may also share information with companies that operate our websites and apps.</p>
    
    <p><strong>We will share this information with our business partners.</strong>
    For example, we may share information with social media sites.  To control this, read the choices section below.</p>
    
    <p><strong>We will share this information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.</strong> For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.</p>
    
    <p><strong>We may share this information with any successor to all or part of our business.</strong>
    For example, if part of our business is sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.</p>
    
    <p><strong>We may share this information for other reasons we may describe to you.</strong></p>
    
    <h3 id="choices" name="choices">You have certain choices about our Mobile Service sharing and marketing practices.</h3>
    <p><strong>You can control cookies and tracking tools.</strong>
    Your mobile browser may give you the ability to control cookies.  How you do so depends on the type of cookie.  Certain browsers can be set to clear past and reject future cookies.  If you block cookies on your browser, certain features on our mobile website may not work.</p>
    
    <p><strong>You can control tools on your mobile devices.</strong>
    For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone.  If your phone allows, you can change app-specific location settings. </p>
    
    <p><strong>You can opt out of receiving our marketing texts and emails.</strong>
    To stop receiving our promotional emails or texts, follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us.  Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we may still send you transactional messages.  These include responses to your questions or information about your account.</p>
    
    <h3>These Mobile Services and children.</h3>
    <p>Our Mobile Service is meant for adults and is not directed to children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us at <a href="mailto:mobileprivacy@discover.com">mobileprivacy@discover.com</a>. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this Privacy Statement. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request."</p>
    
    <h3>We use standard security measures on our Mobile Services.</h3>
    <p>To protect your personal information from unauthorized access, we use security measures that comply with federal law, including computer safeguards.  However, the Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our Mobile Services will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.</p>
    
    <h3>We store information in the United States.</h3>
    <p>If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. Our Mobile Services and associated practices are subject to applicable U.S. laws.</p>
    
    <h3>Our Mobile Services may link to third party services or apps that we don\'t control.</h3>
    <p>If you click on a link to a third-party site, you will be taken to websites or apps we do not control.  This includes social media sites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the privacy practices of these websites. Read the privacy policy of other websites and carefully. We are not responsible for these third party practices.</p>
    
    <h3>We may update this Mobile Privacy Statement.</h3>
    <p>From time to time we may change our Privacy Statement. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Statement as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website and within the Mobile Services.  Please check periodically for updates.</p>
    
    <h3>Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.</h3>
    <p>If you have any questions about this Mobile Privacy Statement, please email us at <a href="mailto:mobileprivacy@discover.com">mobileprivacy@discover.com</a> or call us at <a href="tel://18003472683">1-800-347-2683</a>. </p>
    <p>You can also write to us at:</p>
    <p>Customer Service - Privacy Inquiries<br/>
    Discover Financial Services<br/>
    P.O. Box 30943<br/>
    Salt Lake City, UT  84130-0943</p>
    
    <p>Mobile Privacy Statement last updated January 23, 2013</p>

    <div style="text-align:center; font-size:9pt;"><a href="method://cardProvideFeedback" style="color:#0267b1; text-decoration:none">Provide Feedback</a></div><br/><br/>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="card_terms_of_use">
<![CDATA[<p>The Discover Card and the Discover Bank Mobile Site and Application (&quot;Mobile Service&quot;) provides you with access to certain information regarding your Discover Card account(s), including, without limitation, account balance, recent payments, payment due date, and available credit; and your Discover Bank deposit account(s), including account balance inquiries, internal/external balance transfers, bill payment, and mobile check deposit to most deposit accounts from certain mobile devices. The Mobile Service also allows you to make payments to your Discover Card account through our Mobile Service from certain mobile devices.  By accessing our Mobile Service, you agree to the following Mobile Terms of Use. If you do not agree to these Mobile Terms of Use, do not access this Mobile Service. DFS reserves the right to change these Mobile Terms of Use at anytime and without notice, and your continued use of this Mobile Service constitutes agreement to all such changes. &quot;DFS&quot; means Discover Products Inc., Discover Bank and their affiliates.</p>


    <p><b>Use of this Service</b><br/>
    This Mobile Service is intended for personal, non-commercial use. You may not modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, frame, create derivative works from, transfer, or otherwise use in any other way for commercial or public purposes in whole or in part any information, software, products or services obtained from this Mobile Service, except for the purposes expressly provided herein, without DFS\' prior written approval. Unauthorized use of this Mobile Service and or any DFS systems, including, but not limited to, unauthorized entry into DFS\' systems, misuse of passwords or misuse of any other information, is strictly prohibited. You may not use this Mobile Service in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair any DFS site or service or interfere with any other party\'s use and enjoyment of any DFS site or service. You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any DFS site or service, computer systems or networks connected to any DFS site or service, through hacking, password mining or any other means. You agree that you will not engage in any activities related to this Mobile Service that are contrary to applicable laws or regulations.</p>

    <p>You also agree not to use this Mobile Service or the content or information delivered through the Mobile Service in any way that would violate any law, statute, ordinance or regulation (including, but not limited to, those governing export control, consumer protection, unfair competition, anti-discrimination or false advertising) or in a manner that is false, misleading or inaccurate.</p>

    <p>DFS reserves the right, in its sole discretion, without any obligation and without any notice requirement, to change, improve or correct the information, materials and descriptions on this Mobile Service and to suspend and/or deny access to this Mobile Service for scheduled or unscheduled maintenance, upgrades, improvements or corrections. The information and materials on this Mobile Service may contain typographical errors or inaccuracies. Any dated information is published as of its date only, and DFS does not undertake any obligation or responsibility to update or amend any such information. DFS may discontinue or change any product or service described in or offered on this Mobile Service at any time. DFS also reserves the right to refuse to make any transaction you request through this Mobile Service.  </p>

    <p><b>Consent to Electronic Communications and Costs</b><br/>
    You agree to the use of electronic communications and to transact business electronically through the Mobile Service.  You consent to our contacting you using the Mobile Service, and communicating using text messages, e-mails, and other electronic technologies at the telephone numbers and e-mail addresses that you provide to us.  These communications may relate to the Mobile Service, your Discover Card account, Discover Bank account or other relationships with DFS and its affiliates.  </p>

    <p>You agree that when you use the Mobile Service, you will remain subject to the terms and conditions of all your existing agreements with us, our affiliates, and/or any unaffiliated service providers and your mobile service carrier or provider (e.g., AT&amp;T, Verizon, Sprint, T-Mobile, etc.), and that these Mobile Terms of Use do not amend or supersede any of those agreements. You understand that those agreements may provide for fees, limitations and restrictions which might impact your use of the Mobile Service (for example, your mobile service carrier or provider may impose data usage or text message charges for your use of or interaction with the Mobile Service), and you agree to be solely responsible for all such fees, limitations and restrictions. You agree that only your mobile service carrier or provider is responsible for its products and services. Accordingly, you agree to resolve any problems with your carrier or provider directly with your carrier or provider without involving us.</p>


    <p><b>Disclaimer of Warranty and Limitation of Liability</b><br/>
    THE INFORMATION, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES ON THIS MOBILE SERVICE ARE PROVIDED ON AN &quot;AS IS,&quot; AND &quot;AS AVAILABLE&quot; BASIS. DFS DOES NOT WARRANT THE INFORMATION OR SERVICES PROVIDED HEREIN OR YOUR USE OF THIS MOBILE SERVICE GENERALLY, EITHER EXPRESSLY OR IMPLIEDLY, FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. DFS will not be responsible for any loss or damage that could result from interception by third parties of any information or services made available to you via this Mobile Service. DFS does not warrant that the Mobile Service will work on a wireless device or across the network of a wireless service provider. DFS will not be responsible for or liable to you for: (i) for the capabilities or reliability of any equipment or software used to access the Mobile Service; or (ii) the unavailability of your wireless service, network delays, limitations on wireless coverage, system outages, or interruption of a wireless connection. Your wireless data usage is subject to the fees and terms of your wireless subscriber agreement or data service plan. Although the information provided to you on this Mobile Service is obtained or compiled from sources we believe to be reliable, DFS cannot and does not guarantee the accuracy, validity, timeliness or completeness of any information or data made available to you for any particular purpose. Neither DFS, nor any of its affiliates, directors, officers or employees, nor any third party vendor, will be liable or have any responsibility of any kind for any loss or damage that you incur in the event of any failure or interruption of this Mobile Service, or resulting from the act or omission of any other party involved in making this Mobile Service, the data contained herein or the products or services offered on this Mobile Service available to you, or from any other cause relating to your access to, inability to access, or use of the Mobile Service or these materials, whether or not the circumstances giving rise to such cause may have been within the control of DFS or of any vendor providing software or services. In no event will DFS or any such parties be liable to you, whether in contract or tort, for any direct, special, indirect, consequential or incidental damages or any other damages of any kind even if DFS or any other such party has been advised of the possibility thereof. This limitation on liability includes, but is not limited to, the transmission of any viruses which may infect a user\'s equipment, failure of mechanical or electronic equipment or communication lines, telephone or other interconnect problems (e.g., you cannot access your internet service provider), unauthorized access, theft, operator errors, strikes or other labor problems or any force majeure. DFS cannot and does not guarantee continuous, uninterrupted or secure access to the Mobile Service. You agree to protect and fully compensate us and our affiliates and service providers from any and all third party claims, liability, damages, expenses and costs (including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys fees) caused by or arising from your use of the Mobile Service, or infringement by any other user of your account, of any intellectual property or other right of anyone.</p>

    <p><b>Proprietary Rights</b><br/>
    All right, title and interest in this Mobile Service and any content contained herein is the exclusive property of DFS, except as otherwise stated. You may not modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, frame, create derivative works from, transfer, or otherwise use in any other way for commercial or public purposes in whole or in part any information, software, products or services obtained from this Mobile Service, except for the purposes expressly provided herein, without DFS\' prior written approval. If you copy or download any information or software from this Mobile Service, you agree that you will not remove or obscure any copyright or other notices or legends contained in any such information.</p>

    <p>DISCOVER, CASHBACK BONUS, and the other trademarks, logos, and service marks displayed on this Mobile Service (collectively the &quot;Trademarks&quot;) are the trademarks of Discover Financial Services or their respective third-party owners. Under no circumstances may you alter, modify, or change these Trademarks. You are prohibited from using the Trademarks for any purpose including, but not limited to use as metatags on other pages or sites on the World Wide Web without the written permission of DFS or such third party, which may own the Trademarks.</p>

    <p>Pursuant to Section 512(c)(2) of the Copyright Act, DFS designates the following agent to receive notifications of claimed infringement: Roger Bartos, Discover Products Inc., 2500 Lake Cook Road, Riverwoods, IL 60015; fax: (224) 405-3555; legal@discover.com.</p>

    <p>Some DFS products and services may be covered by U.S. Patent Nos. 6,405,181; 6,567,791; 6,718,313; 7,143,063; 7,346,576; 6,324,524; and 6,795,812.</p>

    <p><b>Privacy and Security</b><br/>
    Please see our <a href="cardprivacystatements://navigateToMobilePrivacyStatement">Mobile Privacy Statement</a>.</p>

    <p><b>Miscellaneous</b><br/>
    These Mobile Terms of Use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the state of Illinois, without regard to conflicts of laws provisions. Sole and exclusive jurisdiction for any action or proceeding arising out of or related to these Mobile Terms of Use shall be in an appropriate state or federal court located in the County of Lake, State of Illinois and the parties unconditionally waive their respective rights to a jury trial. Any cause of action you may have with respect to your use of this Mobile Service must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of these Mobile Terms of Use, or a portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to affect the intent of these Mobile Terms of Use, and the remainder of these Mobile Terms of Use shall continue in full force and effect. These Mobile Terms of Use constitutes the entire agreement between DFS and you with respect to these Mobile Services and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications, agreements and understandings between DFS and you with respect to the subject matter hereof.</p>

    <p>These Mobile Terms of Use were last updated December 17, 2012. </p>]]>
    </string>

</resources>