<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string-array name="card_travel_faq_array">
        <item>@string/card_travel_title_one</item>
        <item>@string/card_travel_content_one</item>
        
        <item>@string/card_travel_title_two</item>
        <item>@string/card_travel_content_two</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_travel_title_three</item>
        <item>@string/card_travel_content_three</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_travel_title_four</item>
        <item>@string/card_travel_content_four</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_travel_title_five</item>
        <item>@string/card_travel_content_five</item>  
        
        <item>@string/card_travel_title_six</item>
        <item>@string/card_travel_content_six</item>  
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="card_travel_title_one">What is 24/7 Travel Assistance?</string>
    <string name="card_travel_content_one">
        24/7 Travel Assistance provides you with a wide range of free travel assistance benefits while you are traveling. 
        You can access the emergency services 24/7 by calling 1-800-DISCOVER (1-800-347-2683) or 1-801-902-3100 if you are outside the U.S.
    </string>
     
    <string name="card_travel_title_two">What benefits are included with 24/7 Travel Assistance? </string>
    <string name="card_travel_content_two">
        <![CDATA[<b>Lost Luggage Tracking:</b> We will help you locate lost luggage by staying in touch with your airline or other carrier, and provide regular status updates until your luggage is found.
		\n<b>Emergency Cash Transfer:</b> We will help you find the most easily obtainable funds and can locate ATMs and financial service institutions, or arrange to have cash wired or delivered while traveling.
		\n<b>Passport and Travel Document Replacement:</b> If your passport, identity cards or other papers necessary to return home are lost or stolen, our provider will offer assistance to replace them.
		\n<b>Flight Rebooking/Ticket Replacement:</b> If your tickets home are lost or stolen, or if illness or other emergency requires changing travel arrangements, our provider offers assistance replacing or rebooking your tickets.\n 
		\nLog into Discover.com to view all your travel benefits.]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_travel_title_three">Where is my Discover card accepted outside of the U.S.?</string>
    <string name="card_travel_content_three">
        Discover cards are currently accepted in multiple countries around the world through the Discover Network and our Network 
        Partnerships: China Union Pay, JCB, and Diners Club International. Please visit our Country Acceptance Map on discover.com 
        to select your travel destination from a full list of countries where Discover is accepted.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_travel_title_four">How do I contact the card service center when traveling outside of the U.S.?</string>
    <string name="card_travel_content_four">
        We are open 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. While outside of the U.S., you can reach us by calling 001 plus 801-902-3100.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_travel_title_five">What should I do if my card is lost or stolen while traveling abroad?</string>
    <string name="card_travel_content_five">
        If your card is lost or stolen while traveling outside of the U.S. 
        immediately contact the Customer Service Center in the U.S. by dialing 001 plus 801-902-3100.
    </string>
    
    <string name="card_travel_title_six">How will foreign transactions appear on my statement?</string>
    <string name="card_travel_content_six">
        Line 1 includes:
		\n-Name and location of the merchant and amount of transaction in U.S. dollars

		\n\nLine 2 includes:
		\n-The amount of the transaction in the foreign currency
    </string>
    
</resources>